[men clamoring]
[all continue clamoring]
[men whispering indistinctly]
[whispering continues]
-[whispering]
-[tapping hammer]
[speaking softly]
[whispering excitedly]
[machine beeping]
[doctor] Now reaching
the right side of the colon.
That looks pretty clean.
And there's the ileocecal valve
which is patent,
and it looks fine.
Prep looks good.
Looks like he's well cleaned out.
Going up the sigmoid colon.
A few scattered diverticula there.
Heading towards the splenic flexure now.
That looks clean.
In the mid transverse colon.
Wait a second.
That looks like a flat polyp there.
Probably about 2 cm.
Gonna take some biopsies of that.
-Yussi, I'm a block away.
-[Yussi] Where  the fuck are you, man?
I told you I'm walking already.
I got two guys, they said they're gonna
be watching the business,
-what the fuck's going on?
-Hey!
Who do you think you're talking to?
-They keep saying they're friends of Arno.
-Arno? Tell 'em I'm coming up now!
Arvi, I need that.
[buzzer sounds]
[man] 30 inches. That's like
about 35 carats in there.
That's an SI1.
[buzzer sounds]
Then right in the middle--
-[man 2] You hear that shit?
-[man 3] Impressive piece.
Yo, Howard. What's popping? This my nigga
Cash I'm always telling you about.
Yeah, man. Gotta cash out.
How do you feel?
It was good.
They'll call me with the results.
[Demany] Get some face on.
-Hi. How are you?
-[Cash] Good, man.
Congratulations. Respect.
He took me to Flawless
to come spend some money with you.
He told me you had the best prices.
[Howard] He's doing you a favor,
believe me,
-that guy's a fuckin' moron.
-[chattering]
Yeah, Arno's friends here. I'm, uh...
Yussi told me you were waiting on me,
I'm sorry about that.
-I'm Howard.
-Phil.
[Howard] You didn't bring 'em any water?
I'm good on the water. I don't really
need water. Thank you anyway.
This is...
This is our own spring water.
We're the first on the block to have that.
-Your parents happy for you?
-[Cash] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right. So, I gotta tell you
I'm in a bit of a rush.
I've not much time because I gotta go--
[Phil] What did I tell you?
I said, "No water."
Didn't I tell you "no water"?
I think it's in your best interest
that you find some time for you and I.
[Howard] Let me get you that.
-[Phil] All right. We're on the same page.
-We're on the same page.
-You all right?
-[Howard] Oh, yeah. 100% fine.
It's good. I'll handle it.
I'll handle it. It's good.
-[man] We don't do that here, sir.
-[Phil speaks indistinctly]
[line ringing]
[Phil] Get that door.
[door closes]
Let him do his thing.
[Arno on voicemail] Arno Moradian.
-[female voice] Is not available.
-He's not answering.
He knows you're calling.
He doesn't wanna deal with you.
-I understand.
-I don't think you do understand.
Come on.
It's not a fucking soap opera.
-Listen, listen. Enough.
-Don't move.
What we doing? What the fuck--
-There you go again. Stop fighting me.
-This is not necessary.
[Phil] It isn't?
We'll be the judge of that.
[Nico] What the fuck is this?
$1200. Literally my last amount of cash...
-[Phil] Fuckin' magician.
-...that I have.
[Phil] What about this?
-This is not mine.
-[Phil laughs]
-Take the fucking watch.
-[Howard] Take the fucking watch.
Fucking prick.
[Arno on voicemail] Arno Moradian.
-[female voice] Is not available--
-Arno, what the fuck is this shit?
You're sending collectors
to fuck with me at my office?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I'm literally minutes away from closing
the biggest deal of my goddamn life,
and when I do you're gonna be embarrassed!
[chatting indistinctly]
Oh, and by the way,
the watch they took from me,
it's worth $20,000.
I want that deducted from the 100 grand.
Do you understand? Call me back!
Look at this. What's up, ladies?
[whispers] Shh. She's sleeping.
She's sleeping.
[woman laughs]
[muffled chatter]
[Howard] Bullshit.
-Hey, Howie.
-Hey, how are you?
People coming in and out
of the apartment.
-[Julia] Oh, my God! Not this song.
-You show up to work any time you please.
Howard, I was working all night.
I'm sick of this shit.
You're taking advantage of me!
Oh, Howard! Oh, my God! Howard!
It's 10:30. It's time to wake up!
You're so extra.
Did you have a party last night?
I did not! Did we have a party?
Why didn't you call me?
Okay, because I did call you,
at around 9:30.
You said, "I'll call you back in five."
I waited for hours--
Because I fell asleep.
-I was putting Beni to sleep.
-That's rude.
-Here we go with the lies.
-I had to put him to sleep. I'm not lying!
-You're so manipulative!
-I fell asleep on the floor, again!
I'm exhausted!
Well, I didn't ask you to have kids.
It's not my fault you have kids.
Oh, shut the fuck up with that.
Look, do you wanna fucking stay mad
or do you wanna get in bed and cuddle?
I know you wanna cuddle, Howard.
Just come here.
-[Kat] Come on.
-Come on, just come here.
Come here, baby. Come on.
Come on, I know you wanna come here.
-[Howard] I'm so goddamn stressed out.
-I know you can't resist me.
I know you can't resist me. Come on.
Mwah.
Don't, don't, don't.
You can't just do that.
[softly] Just come here. Just one kiss.
Wanna see the photos I took?
-Yes.
-[Kat] Look at this one.
-[Howard] What was the shoot?
-[Kat] She looks amazing.
[Julia] I took these pictures,
I think I have a future in that.
-[Howard] How much did you get?
-[Julia] 3,500.
And who's this guy?
-[Julia] The Weeknd.
-[Kat] He's major.
[Howard] What the fuck is "The Weeknd"?
[Julia] He's gonna be major.
Even though he's from Canada.
This guy looks stupid.
[shop bell jingles]
-Hi.
-[woman] Hi.
-How are you?
-Nice to meet you.
Howard Ratner, how are you?
Good to see you.
I have a piece.
You know this kid, The Weeknd?
That's Michael Jackson there on the cross.
Gonna be a controversial piece.
Makes it more valuable.
The blacks are VS2s, that's platinum.
Turn around, don't even step in my place.
Turn around.
-[Howard] I got bets. 24 Gs.
-Don't sit down!
24 Gs. Where would you get 24 Gs?
I want the old KC Lakers.
I want the fucking over, all right?
-I want Kobe's under 'cause--
-Kobe under.
-All of a sudden he's passing--
-Just throw it in the ocean..
[Howard] He's not scoring tonight.
-I want the Sixers to cover.
-[cell phone vibrating]
[Gary] Plus one.
-The points--
-Let's finish the bet.
-Hey, one thing at a time. Come on now!
-I gotta run these points.
-[Demany] Yo!
-Demany.
-KG said any minute.
-Can we finish the bet?
If he gets to the store before I do,
you just fucking keep him there.
-Better get here soon, he's gonna be--
-You promise me?
Kevin Garnett is coming
to my fucking showroom.
-Can we finish the bet?
-Right now!
[female automated voice]
Fifth floor, going up.
[Phil] We got every right
to fucking be here.
Ask the owner. Fuck you!
[bodyguard] You and your man get--
-Whoa, whoa!
-Get your man and get the fuck out!
[Howard] Hey, hey, hey, get out.
-Get the fuck out.
-[all clamoring]
-[bodyguard] What?
-Fuck you, man!
[Phil] You just got involved
in something you shouldn't have.
-Fuck is going on?
-[Phil] Hear me? That's on you, asshole.
-I--
-[Phil] You see this?
I don't know these fucking guys.
You're dead, fucker. You're dead.
-I--
-[Phil] You think I'm playing games?
-Get your laugh off now, asshole.
-[Howard] But I didn't do nothing.
When I'm shoveling the dirt
over your fucking head,
we'll see how funny it is then!
[David] I have clients in the office.
Disgraceful.
Turn around and walk away.
[Howard] We're good.
David, go back inside.
-Everything's fine.
-You sure?
-Turn around and walk away!
-[Howard] That's my...
-That's my shop.
-[man] Everybody back in.
-Hello, open the door.
-[man] Let's go.
-[buzzer sounds]
-Okay. Jesus.
You with KG?
Okay, well, you gotta shut that door.
It's KG, huh?
-Is that closed?
-[buzzer sounds]
[KG] That's my man?
[man 1] This is insane,
they just beat Yussi up.
Howard, Howard,
what the fuck is going on, man?
They tried to fuck Yussi up.
Look at his shirt...
Look at his fucking shirt.
Look at his shirt!
-[Howard] Okay.
-[man 2] ...it's a yellow...
Listen, hey, thanks
for the security, by the way.
Send those bitches back
to Paramus or Bay Ridge, yeah.
You take that and charge it up for me?
All I got is fucking Yussi to protect me.
[indistinct chatter]
-Yo, yo. Hey, let us talk.
-What's good with you, man?
What's up? What's up with the...
Did Amar'e have fucking time on the clock?
Come on, no time on the clock.
-[Howard] You're waving him off.
-[KG] You serious?
-Referee right now?
-[Howard] Come on.
-I like the earrings.
-You like these?
-Those look great.
-I was checking out some rings.
-Last time you cleaned 'em?
-Talking about?
-[Howard] Let me clean this for you.
-He can clean 'em real quick.
Let me throw 'em
in the ultrasonic for you for free.
[KG] What's this gonna cost me?
-[Howard] For free.
-For real?
Won't cost nothing.
The fuck you talking-- Nah.
I'd think you'd have
bigger rocks than that.
-You're a big guy.
-[man 2] That's why we're here.
See what y'all got in here.
[Howard] Who'd win in a fight?
Ben Wallace or Tony Allen?
-TA all day.
-[Howard] Oh, yeah?
-Look at this shit here.
-What is that?
[man 4] ...the fuck out of here.
What's that, a gremlin?
Iced-out gremlin down here?
-This ugly motherfucker right here--
-[Howard] Furby?
[Demany] ...animal
or some kind of fucking...
Some toy, or some shit,
and he'll just bling the bitch out.
I bling this.
Used to work with niggas
on early music videos, all that shit.
He like the first nigga to start all that.
-Are you serious?
-I started this shit.
-[Demany] Show him the eyes.
-Yeah.
All right, so I did this.
So it fucks with you.
[all laugh]
-Are you serious?
-[Howard] There it is.
[laughter continues]
How's that? How's that?
-It scares the shit out of people.
-[KG] Look at that.
[Demany] It's a fucking
older model, but it's dope.
-[Howard] Listen...
-[man 3] You could put that shit back.
-This shit was slamming.
-[KG] I gotta...
What's the length?
Let me see the chain on that.
-That's an 18, but I can get you a 14.
-[KG] Look like a Gremlin or something.
[Howard] KG. Doc know you're here,
by the way?
No, he doesn't.
And let's keep it that way.
It's game night.
You should be stretching out.
-[Demany] Fucking insane, man.
-What is he, a coach?
-Just a fucking crazy-ass Jew.
-[man 3] T, look at this shit.
[Howard] Throw these in the ultrasonic.
-As soon as the other stuff is done.
-No, now.
-We got a nigga that's--
-[Howard] KG, I wouldn't lean on that.
-Yo.
-I wouldn't lean on it.
Kevin was telling me
he looking for watches.
-You looking for watches?
-Uh-huh.
Let's go to the wall of watches
right there... What are we talking? AP?
-I was thinking about the Prezi.
-Right.
That one you got
that crazy-ass deal for?
That one for 16.
That crazy one though. You know?
Yeah. The, uh, 16, yeah,
you're right. Right.
[KG] The Prezi.
-Look at this, right here.
-[woman] Wow, okay.
-Boom.
-Right.
That's a small watch for a big man.
-[Demany] Look at the detail in there.
-Yeah.
-You got papers for this?
-[Howard] No, hey...
-Of course--
-I don't have a box or papers.
I don't have either one.
What are you talking about?
-You sold me this shit, dummy.
-[Howard] I don't remember that.
Listen, niggas call
niggas out for this, man.
Of course.
If you don't have the box or pap--
You find me one nigga
with a KMH watch they call out.
-Huh?
-[Howard] It's a moot point,
Demany, because
I don't have these, all right?
So how about we move on
to the diamonds here?
Listen, you got a girl?
Why don't you get your girl a treat?
[Julia] He doesn't have a girlfriend.
-[KG] Says who?
-Says you.
-Hey.
-[KG] How you know if I got a girlfriend?
Howard, get the fuck over here.
-[Julia] 'Cause you told me.
-[KG] I never said that.
-[Demany] What are you doing?
-What's up?
Why didn't you bring
the goddamn watches out?
-I'm not doing that.
-The nigga would have bought one.
I told you,
you can keep 'em in my safe.
I don't want you selling 'em
out of my showroom. You understand me?
Fucking dumbass. Where the fuck am I gonna
sell 'em, nigga? On the goddamn street?
-That's not my problem.
-That ain't your problem?
-No--
-That ain't--
He don't like shit in this dusty
motherfucking tin-foil filled--
Yes, he does. He's having
a fucking ball here. What are you--
What the fuck is he gonna buy?
A goddamn Furby, nigga?
Fuck you. All right?
I'ma take his ass to Flawless,
I'm not fucking with you today.
-You're not taking them to Flawless.
-Since you acting like a bitch--
KG, do me a favor?
Don't lean on that, please.
[doorbell chimes]
-[Demany] You acting stupid.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Okay.
Buzz him in, buzz him in now. Now.
[buzzer sounds]
Oh, my God, is this...
This is it! This is it.
-Hey.
-What's up?
[Howard] Okay, look at this.
A package from Fishtonic,
where you want this?
Bring it in, go to my office.
KG? Don't you dare leave, okay?
What's in this package
is gonna blow your mind, KG.
-Is it heavy?
-Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Oh, my God.
What you got? Give me that.
[knocks]
[muffled chatter]
-Man, I can't do this anymore, bro.
-What happened?
What happened? Your street goons,
they attacked me.
[Howard] What did you say
to piss them off?
Listen, Garnett's crew came in here,
they took a look around,
see these guys, they're like,
"Who works here? Who doesn't?
Who doesn't, get out."
I said, "These guys don't work here."
That was stupid.
You shouldn't have said that.
These guys grabbed me,
dragged me over the counter,
ripped my shirt,
got me looking like a fool.
Here. Take this. That's a Gucci shirt.
It's $500, it's brand new.
Are you fucking serious right now?
-The tag's still on it.
-It ain't about the shirt.
I gave you eight years of my life,
look how you treat me.
I put in everything into this business.
I saved your ass a thousand times.
I can't take this place anymore, man.
I can't deal with your problems
every other day.
There's a lot of people on this block
that would love to do business with me.
When you see me working with them,
you're not gonna like it, gonna be jealous.
You're not gonna like it, Howard.
Howard? Hello.
I'm standing here, man.
There's a lot of people I could be doing
business with other than you.
You're falling apart.
You're looking like a fool out here
in the Diamond District.
Looking through fucking fish.
Come on,
I gave you eight years of my life
and you can't even fucking talk to me
and look me in the eyes?
Man to fucking man?
Holy shit, I'm gonna cum.
Hey, fuck you, man.
I'm finished with this shithole.
Hey, yo, KG? KG?
-Yo. Hey.
-Howard, Yussi is gone.
-That's fine with me.
-Gone for good.
Let me get a phone from you.
KG, you've gotta come here. All right?
-I gotta show you something.
-I gotta leave soon.
-I know. Listen to me.
-I gotta get out.
Okay, so I'm watching TV
like a year ago, all right.
I'm watching one of those History Channel
shows, trying to learn shit.
And I stumble...
-You ever hear of African Jews?
-African Jews?
-Yeah. No?
-[Demany laughing]
-Nigga want everybody to be a Jew.
-Check this out, I know, all right?
So these are black Jews. All right?
They're stranded in the middle
of Ethiopia. It's deep shit.
-Stranded?
-Yeah, lookit.
They got nothing.
They don't got cars, they don't got shit.
And I'm watching this, and I'm like,
"What are these guys wearing?"
Look, it's on the Torah there,
it's everywhere, right?
It's a fuck-- Where do these fucking guys
get precious black opals?
-That's what that is.
-It's a black opal?
I do my research.
These guys live near the Welo mines,
which primarily is red opal.
-Which aren't worth shit.
-Okay.
But these, you can't get your hands
on these things, you understand?
[KG] Really?
So, look. I say to myself,
"How do I get a hold of these guys?"
And I've managed to track these guys down.
I buy one from 'em.
-[KG] Holy... What is that? [laughs]
-What is that? That's right here.
That's the rock. That's the rock.
That's the stone. I got this.
-[KG] Look how it's winking in the light.
-[Demany] How you get this shit?
It took me 17 months
to get this thing, okay?
-[KG] Holy...
-[Howard] Just look at this. Hang on.
Go through my loupe. Be careful.
That's my best loupe.
Let's see this...
-[Howard] Look at it.
-[Demany] You're into that motherfucker.
[KG] Oh, wow.
-[Howard] Isn't that the shit?
-[KG] What?
-That's history right there. Understand?
-How many carats is this?
A good, what, 4- 5,000 carats?
$3,000 a carat?
-[KG] What?
-I'm not fucking bullshitting you.
-Why's it got so many colors in it?
-[Howard] That's the thing.
They say you can see
the whole universe in opals,
that's how fucking old they are.
-[KG] Holy snap...
-[Howard] I'm telling you.
-That's why I wanted you to see it.
-I gotta have this.
[Demany] Your ass crazy, man.
From stone to stone.
Garnet's a stone, you know that.
That's a million-dollar opal
you're holding.
Straight from the Ethiopian Jewish tribe.
I mean, this is old-school
Middle-earth shit.
[Demany] Got a motherfucking
dinosaur gem in this...
[Howard] The dinosaurs, that's right,
the dinosaurs fucking stared
at this thing.
It's 110 million years old. At the least.
-Some deep shit.
-[Demany] Fuck basketball.
[Howard] Can't lean on the glass, KG.
[man 1] Oh. Shit.
-[clamoring]
-[Howard] Fuck.
-You all right?
-[KG] Yeah.
I told you not to lean.
-Get a towel or something.
-[KG] Chill. I'm good.
You heard me. I did tell him
not to lean. You all right?
[Demany] Don't cut your fucking self.
-Give him a napkin.
-That's a sign. That's a sign I need this.
That's what this is.
-[man] Make sure my nigga good.
-[KG] Straight.
[Howard] Fucking glass,
it's a lot of weight you were putting...
That's a sign. I need this.
-I need this right here.
-I-- Listen, it's not for sale.
I can't sell it to you.
-What do you mean, it's not for sale?
-I can't do it. That...
-God damn it, it's set for auction.
-[Julia] Just give it to him.
Why the fuck would you show me something
if I couldn't have it?
The fuck would you bring this out?
I was excited,
decided to share it with you.
Let me hold it for a night then.
Let me wear it to the game tomorrow.
It would be cool, I'm going to the game,
I'll grab it from you,
then meet you at Adley's
tomorrow morning, first thing.
Cool, boom, just like that. It's perfect.
-[Demany] Come on.
-[Julia] One night.
-[KG] You serious?
-I can't.
-[Julia] It's one night.
-They'll pull it from the auction...
-[KG] You don't understand.
-[man] Come on, man.
[KG] This stone,
I'm really connecting with this.
I feel like I'ma have
40 or 50 on this, man.
-[man 1] Man...
-[man 2] That energy.
-[man 1] Yeah, boy.
-You understand?
-[man 2] Yeah.
-[KG] Understand that?
[Demany] That's what I'm talking about.
This shit speaking to him.
[KG] I'ma destroy Philly tonight
with this.
-[Demany] Inspiring.
-[KG] Bitch-ass niggas. This fucking thing
-makes me feel like I can fly.
-Shit.
-[Demany] Hear that?
-[man] Let him get that.
You're going to @me at HowieBling.
-Yes.
-[Howard] 30 fucking pics I want liked.
-Yes, I got you.
-[Demany] You talking about @me.
[Howard] Let me get a fucking shot.
-[Demany] That's a good idea, my nigga.
-Come here.
-[KG] Phew. Jump in here.
-So you hold it up.
[Demany] Get me in that bitch, too.
-[Howard] Boom.
-[KG] Boom.
-Cool.
-[man] Yes.
-All right.
-[KG] All right.
I can't just--
-Give me the Celtic ring. I want the ring.
-[Demany] Come the fuck on.
-Collateral. Make sure he brings it back.
-No. He's good money.
-I know he's good for it.
-[KG] Know what? That's a deal.
-[Howard] Wanna make sure he remembers.
-[KG] I give you that.
[Howard] Thanks. All right,
I'll keep it right here.
-Next to my Knicks '73, classic.
-[KG] Classic, I like that.
-[Howard] I appreciate your understanding.
-Gotcha, right.
All right, listen, you meet me at...
[Demany] I'll meet your happy ass. Yes.
[Howard] You will fucking bring
that stone to me 9:00 in the morning.
Listen to me, no dicking around.
You'll show up, you hear me?
Chill. I'll see you there, motherfucker.
-All right, let's roll. Let's do it.
-[man] You better have 50 tonight.
-[KG] I'm outta here.
-Buzz 'em out.
-[buzzer sounds]
-I got his earrings.
The earrings. Wait! Bring it out to him.
-Keep 'em till tomorrow, I'll grab 'em.
-[Howard] KG, no.
-Black Jew power, nigga. He's so extra.
-[clicks tongue]
Fucking, I don't know.
What the fuck--
Who's gonna clean this fucking shit?
[buzzer sounds]
Eddie boy, what are you doing?
What do you want, Dad?
Look what I got. Look,
you're gonna love this. Here, hey.
-[man] Howard.
-[Howard] What's that there?
Will you leave me alone?
-What is it?
-This is Kevin Garnett's ring.
Championship ring, NBA 2008.
I knew you'd freak out.
Sick.
-All right, I love you, my boy.
-All right, bye.
Alberto. Came to work.
-Bronstein.
-[Bronstein] Hey, Howard.
Hey. Break out your tray,
where is it? Where is it?
-Got the tray. What you got?
-I'd shake your hand,
but I know where it's been. Look at this.
It's Kevin Garnett's
2008 Championship ring.
-Championship ring?
-[Howard] Championship ring. 2008.
You wanna pawn it or sell it?
I wanna pawn it, I wanna pawn it.
-Let me take a look.
-I don't know what you're looking for.
-[Steve] Check the diamonds.
-[Howard] It was just on his finger.
It's single cut. It's not even full cut.
-[Howard] Talk to the league...
-Steve, take a look.
-...about the way they cut their shit.
-But they're worth less.
Take a look at this. All right?
[Bronstein] It's his ring. I understand.
[Howard] That's from his Instagram.
It's blowing up right now.
I hear you. So what do you need for it?
I figure that thing's worth 80 grand?
Just loan it to me. That's it.
Float it to me. I'll be back Friday.
Number one,
we both know what's in here.
We both know the value is mostly
'cause it's memorabilia.
It is a memorabilia piece.
-That's why you're gonna sell it, right?
-[Steve] So, I tell you what.
Give me 50 Gs. Just float it to me.
I'm gonna give you $25,000,
but I want an 8% vig on the ring.
Eight percent? Fucking--
How about I give you a grand?
You can take a grand off the top.
I'm gonna come back Friday for it.
Last time, you left something here
for six months.
We wanna make sure up front.
Last time wasn't my fault.
We fucking went over that.
I understand.
Let's make it quick. $21,000, 7% vig,
and I want you to know,
you say you'll be back Friday.
If you're not back Friday, it's my ring.
[Howard] If I don't bring it back Friday,
I'm a dead man, so...
[Bronstein] We have a deal?
-All right, deal.
-[Steve] Deal.
-[Bronstein] Mazel.
-[Howard] Mazel.
-All right. Mazel.
-[Steve] Mazel.
-[Howard] Go to the safe?
-[Bronstein] Get him the money.
-[Howard] Thank you.
-[Bronstein] We'll get the money.
[Howard] Good Pesach. This is great.
[Arno on phone] 70th and 1st.
The fuck is he doing there?
Just walking. Now he's stopping.
He's slowing down.
[Arno] Why?
[Phil] He's doing something.
Playing with his phone or something.
He's playing with something,
I can't make it out.
I can't see him, his back is to me.
He's hunched over, you can't see.
[Phil] I dunno, we can't see anything.
Oh! Now, here he goes,
here he goes. He's going again.
Wait, I just got a text from him.
-What's he saying?
-It's a picture of money.
-This fucking prick.
-He says, "Arno..."
He's got fucking money.
"...I got your money right here."
-[Phil] He's turning in somewhere.
-[Nico] A restaurant. Nino's.
-Hey, handsome, where's he at?
-He's in the back.
He's in the back.
[customers chattering]
Hey. You got him making meatballs
in the back? All right.
-You have your romaine, croutons...
-[Howard] Gary.
-Gary, sorry.
-...you have your eggs.
No carrots in the Caesar salad.
What do you want?
I already made your bet.
I know. I gotta change the bet.
I got $21,000 here,
so you add it onto the 19 grand.
$40,000 in all.
-Scrap the whole bet?
-Scrap the whole bet.
I wanna make a six-way parlay,
Celtics, Sixers game. What's the line out?
-Still plus one.
-Plus one. I want the Celtics to cover.
I want the Celtics halftime,
I want Garnett points and rebounds.
-Garnett blocked shots.
-Right.
Celtics opening tip.
Do you take lightning bets?
-Yeah, but you don't want any part.
-Fine.
A thousand dollars a point, okay?
Take this, and this is a gift from me.
[Gary] What's this?
[Howard] For just tolerating me
for all this time, okay?
No, no. I already have a Rolex.
I don't need your watch.
It probably fell off a truck anyway.
Listen.
Garnett this, Garnett that,
what do you know?
I don't know, I just know.
Well, I'll tell you what I know. It's the
dumbest fucking bet I ever heard of.
I disagree.
I disagree, Gary.
[announcer] Celtics don't have a point.
[Howard] Shoot. Let him shoot.
Let him shoot. Yeah, go, go. Go.
-Oh, fuck!
-[announcer] Jrue Holiday.
Fuck!
Who came out of four games...
Fucking-- That's five
fucking steps he took.
[cell phone vibrates]
...hitting four of six
from three-point range.
Jesus Christ!
Celtics feel that they stole game one
at home, if such a thing is possible.
That's it. Tuck to KG. Finish it.
Back him now, back him now.
Boom! Fuck you.
Yes. That's it. That's it.
That's my man!
Go, get up on him.
Get up on him. Fucking...
Get the fuck up on him, God damn it!
Howard, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Howard, Beni's waiting for you.
Okay. I'm coming up.
It's 25 minutes past his bedtime. Go.
Did he brush his teeth yet?
Brush his teeth? I've sent you
seven texts in the dark.
-Howard!
-Yeah.
It's the first quarter.
That guy was in my shop
earlier today.
Look at him. Soft touch.
-Hit that shit. Boom!
-I don't care. Say goodnight to your son.
...jumpers that got him 29 points.
Let me get up there.
...with the fall-away.
Basket counts and a foul.
I'll be right there.
Okay, let me just get to a time-out.
...Kevin Garnett are gonna be...
-This fucking ref is ridiculous.
-Now!
All right! All right, all right.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. God fucking damn.
[commercial break jingle
plays on TV]
[announcer speaking indistinctly]
-...with three minutes to go.
-[crowd chanting]
And Garnett will put it up
with four on the shot block...
-[grunts]
-...and hit.
Garnett, vintage game one, for sure.
Fifteen points on seven for eight
from the field.
[quietly] Oh, no.
Oh, give me a fucking break.
Fuck, you...
[muttering]
[indistinct basketball
commentary on TV]
[announcer] Here's Jrue Holiday
from traffic with a turnaround...
-[Howard] Hi, hey, hey.
-[Eddie] Garnett's killing it.
I know.
Beni's sleeping, keep it down.
I'm sorry. Just so hyped.
NBA's always the last
two fucking minutes, so let's calm down.
-[Eddie] Okay.
-[Howard] Hit that, KG.
'Bout to win money.
Jason's about to pay me 25 bucks
for the first half, double it up,
last half I'm making 50 bucks.
Your father bet a lot of money
on this one.
Really? How much?
-How much?
-You don't wanna know.
-A lot though, right?
-Yes.
Put that shit in the fucking hole!
That's right, go on, you can dunk again.
Boom. Boom. Boom. All right.
Fucking amazing. That's fucking amazing.
All right?
-[TV playing]
-He's down. He's asleep.
[woman on TV] ...but no. He's like, you
can page, you can follow your hobbies,
and your bliss and your
entrepreneurial thing
and Stephanie and Annaliese
went, "Ooh."
What would you do
if you had two weeks to live?
Uh, that's a good question.
Can you flip-- Can you flip it
to ESPN just for one second?
-[scoffs]
-This is a huge game, that's wh--
That's why he's going
so crazy up there.
Know what? I'm tempted to wrangle
the kids downstairs right now,
and get it over with.
You really wanna do that?
I don't know how sensitive that is.
Oh, you're calling me insensitive?
Thought we both agreed
that we wait till after Passover?
Next, you'll be saying
you wanna wait until after the summer.
Hey, I'm not opposed
to waiting till after summer.
[scoffs]
It's a commercial.
Can you just put the game on
for two fucking minutes?
Till my car gets here.
[remote clicks]
[announcer] Hey,
that's not Chuck the body.
No words can describe that.
[announcer 1] 41, yesterday,
I don't know how old these guys are,
but you can't tell by their age.
[announcer 2] You're saying ages
all older than you are.
[announcer 1] Uh, well, younger
than the num-- ages you just gave.
Crazy. This is crazy.
[announcer 1] KG hitting the shot from
outside. He'll be 36 on Saturday
and he puts the Celtics
over the century mark.
101 to 76. Garnett down to 27...
Oh!
Oh, yes. Oh, God, yes. Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my G--
Oh, my God.
-Hey. Change of plans.
-[driver] What's up?
You wanna go up 3rd or 4th?
Uh, take the exit, 49th Street
and 3rd Ave, Smith and Wollensky's.
-Everything okay?
-I just...
-What's your name?
-Davis.
Davis. I just hit very big, very big.
-Oh, my God.
-[Davis laughs]
My God.
[announcer] Eye contact, spin back
for the alley oop, and if it was a foul,
he was gonna posterize somebody.
KG having fun.
[Howard] Oh, yeah.
Jules?
Hey.
[line ringing]
-[Julia on phone] What's up?
-Baby, where are you at?
I'm just coming back now.
I'm in the elevator. Why, what's up?
I got held up, I'm just on my way back
now. Yeah, Dinah was on a tear tonight.
-Oh, that sucks.
-Yeah.
How far away are you?
I am in the tunnel just getting in there.
-Oh, okay, so you're very close?
-Yes.
Um... Well, hold on,
I gotta go, I gotta go.
-Wait, wait, wait. Hey.
-What?
I can't wait to see you.
I'm in an incredible mood.
I got another line. Gotta go.
-Okay.
-Bye.
[Julia] ...as we speak.
I still have to set up the steaks.
I still have to get ready.
Because his gem came.
Do you not listen to me?
I've been talking about it all day.
I'm gonna wear-- Remember the green,
that I sent you the photo of?
Yeah, I know, I know.
[Julia continues speaking indistinctly]
[typing]
[cell phone chimes]
[camera shutter clicks]
-I'm gonna cum!
-[shrieks]
I'm gonna cum! I can't help it.
I had to get that.
-I had to get that.
-Oh, my God!
-Why the fuck did you do that?
-No, no, you see
how fucking sweet you look.
You look so gorgeous.
-I just hit so fucking big. I hit so big.
-[whispering] How big?
Feel how wet I am.
[both moaning]
[Demany on phone] I'm almost there.
What? You told me that already.
I hit mad traffic. What you want me to do?
We told-- Nine o'clock
we were supposed to be there.
-It's fucking 9:43!
-Look, all the city's clogged up.
I can't do anything about that.
Not everybody's
on Demany time, man.
-I left literally at 7:00 a.m.
-Let's move.
Okay. You can tell Anne we're here.
Sorry, hold on one second. Hi.
-Uh, Anne Duvalle...
-Mm-hmm.
Howard Ratner and his partner.
We're all ready to go.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-When your partner gets here,
-I will let her know that you're both...
-Thanks.
You can sit over there if you'd like.
Yes?
[Demany] Howard,
I'm pulling up right now. Come out.
I... I said I'm inside. I was--
-I'm not gonna find parking...
-Double park the car.
-I'm not getting no fucking ticket...
-Do it!
-...for you or nobody else.
-What the--
Come meet me. I wanna talk to you.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No, I'm not fucking kidding you.
I'm pulling up. Come out.
-Fine.
-Will he have any guests joining him?
-We'll be right back.
-Okay.
Fuck! Fuck! Stupid...
Howard, Howard!
Jesus, how... how'd you find me?
-Your office told me.
-You following me?
-We need the money today.
-My office would never tell you.
-This is the last straw.
-Get outta here.
You haven't been returning
my phone calls or texts.
You can't take ten minutes...
What, you bring
your fucking heavy with you?
-Yeah. You got my money--
-You want money?
-Yeah.
-I got fucking money.
-You owe me 32 grand.
-Fine.
-[Larry] For the games.
-[Howard] There's 30 grand.
Fucking sell that for 15 Gs.
Fifteen Gs? Where am I gonna sell this?
Go to Wempe's, 55th and 5th Avenue,
go there. Put that in your fucking pocket.
-[hip-hop song playing]
-Hey, hey.
Where's it at? Where's the gem?
-Get in real quick.
-Give me the gem, I'll run it upstairs.
-[Demany] Get in. I need to talk to you.
-I don't know anything about a watch.
Hey. Get the fuck out.
I don't want a watch.
You just gave it to me.
For the money you owe me.
Shut the fuck up!
I'm not fucking buying watches now.
-Back the fuck up. Don't touch my shit.
-Look at the license plate.
Walk the fuck away.
Come on, give me the opal.
Get in, my nigga, so I can talk to you.
-They're waiting on us, we're late.
-Get in, we'll talk to him.
-Why am I getting in?
-Get the fuck in.
-[horns blaring]
-[Howard] Jesus Christ.
Get outta here
with that fucking fugazi shit.
-[horns continue blaring]
-Who the fuck are they?
-Why am I in your car?
-All right.
-They're fucking waiting on us.
-So look, listen.
-Where is the opal?
-We're at the hotel,
getting ready to go, we're about
to go party, got three bad bitches...
I don't have time. Where's my opal?
...and KG leaves his fucking ID upstairs.
-The hotel card--
-We don't have time!
They are waiting for us.
Where's the fucking opal?
Garnett got it. All right?
-Garnett's got it? This guy fucked us.
-Fuck.
I don't know what you want me to do.
-You the one--
-Call him on the phone. Lemme talk to him.
I can't fucking call him
right now, he's at practice.
-I'll give him another opal.
-Listen to me.
-For free.
-I can't call him.
-To wear for as long as he wants.
-He is at practice, my nigga.
He's not gonna answer his fucking phone
for me, God, nobody else.
Fine, then we're going to practice.
What? So you want me to go
to fucking Philly right now?
He's in Philly?
Then we're going to Philly.
I just got back from Philly.
I'm not driving--
It's two fucking hours to get there,
come on, come on.
Fucking co--
[hip-hop music continues playing]
-Fuck this, let's go.
-You fucking retarded.
-[Howard] Gotta be in and out.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[cell phone chimes]
-[Howard] Got my daughter's play tonight.
Who is that? Is that KG?
Tell him we're coming in.
Yo. You gotta calm
your happy ass down.
Are we going inside the facility
or we gonna meet him out here?
-Just chill the fuck out.
-I hope we see Rondo there.
Love to tell him "Thank you"
for dropping all those dimes.
Man, no, that's not-- They busy.
What the fuck is it with you
Jewish niggas and basketball, anyway?
Huh? Obsessed.
I'll have you know, the first two points
scored in the NBA was a Jew.
Yeah, yeah. Who was it, Fred Flintstein?
No. Ossie Schectman, 1946,
played for the Knicks.
Here we go. Yeah, this is
where the big boys play.
...always, always
gotta practice, and always got--
Look at this, this is sick. Sick, my God.
Hey, check this out. Yeah.
Cookies.
-[man] Yo, man.
-[Howard] Rondo's coming up.
He can't help himself.
He's gonna have to finish. And he scores.
-[man] Can you give us an update?
-[Demany] I need to get through.
Sorry, brother.
[man] What's changing for game two?
[Howard] Demany?
-[woman] I got one coming back.
-What's up? I'm with him.
-Whoa.
-No, no, I'm with him.
-Demany. What the fuck?
-[woman] Excuse me, excuse me?
What's he fucking...
-Hey, hi.
-I'm with him.
-I came with him.
-You didn't--
-You saw me walk through the door.
-I didn't see you walk through the door.
-What's your name?
-I won't be on a list, I came with him.
-What's your name, sir?
-I came with him.
What the fuck is he doing to me?
Cocksucker fucking works for me.
[Dinah] Is Marcel excited?
-[Eiline] I think she's a little nervous.
-[Dinah] Little, it's the lead play.
[Eiline] I know. We're very proud of her.
Yeah, yeah. And Danny's got a role, too.
-Small part. He's nervous. But...
-But that's good, yeah.
-[Dinah] ...nothing fazes him.
-[Eric] Working?
-He said she was amazing.
-[Howard] Yeah. One second.
-Sure.
-What are you guys doing for the break?
Oh. Um...
We're not doing anything this year.
-[Eiline] Oh, really?
-Yeah.
[Eric] Wow.
-[Eiline] That's not like you guys.
-[Eric] How come?
-Howard, how come? Howard?
-[Eiline] Everything okay?
Howard?
No vacation?
No, we're... next year, we're gonna take
a bigger trip, saving up for that.
-Gonna go to Europe.
-Oh, that's nice.
So, uh, yeah, do a little culture.
These kids are becoming morons.
Well... Tsk.
-Oh, yeah. Well...
-We'll be morons in Cancn.
Right. Especially on the trapeze.
Good luck to Danny tonight.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah.
-We just talked about Danny.
-[Eric] Good.
Okay.
What are you gonna do for Passover?
Is your sister coming?
-Yeah.
-What are you doing? Who you got?
Watching for LeBron. I got six different
people playing six different games.
[Howard] Hey, we're all making sac--
-Hey. Who tapped me? Who was that?
-[Dinah] And I don't cook,
so they give me shit about that.
-[Howard] Who is it?
-[Eiline] Gefilte fish?
[Eiline] That'll be nice.
You gonna do the questions?
[Dinah] Yeah.
[Eiline] The four questions, yeah?
You practicing?
[Beni] I've been practicing.
[Eiline] I don't know how we're gonna keep
it in Mexico with the whole matzah.
-[Dinah] You kidding?
-[Eiline] Yeah.
[Dinah laughs]
[Eiline] Well, good luck to Marcel.
[Dinah] I know, and to Danny.
Where are you going?
Daddy's gotta go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back.
[Dinah] She's gonna be on
in just a second.
I'll be back. Thank you.
Howard. Marcel is about to get on--
[Howard] Okay. I'll be right back.
[Eiline] Everything okay?
-This is fucked up, guys.
-What's so fucked up about it?
Can I speak to you guys outside?
Sure you wanna do that? Yeah?
All right.
Excuse me.
Hey. What are we gonna
do here, man?
-Hey, yo.
-Come on, man.
That's my family!
Get the fuck off, motherf-- [screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
Okay, look out.
You're going to be great.
[door handle rattles]
Are you kidding me,
how good you guys look.
Dad, what are you doing?
-Marcel, break a leg. We're all here...
-What are you doing here?
[panting]
[tires squealing]
Fuck.
[inaudible]
-[man] Get him, get him.
-Fuck.
Fucking shit.
[man] Come here, you motherfucker.
Hey, fuck you. Fuck you!
-Ah, fuck!
-[car horn honking]
[groans]
[man] Come on. Get up.
[Howard] Okay. Come on. I'm walking,
I'm coming. I'm coming.
[Buddy] Get fucked.
[Howard] Hey, what the fuck are you doing?
-Fucking bit me. You fucking cocksucker.
-[Howard] Arno. Hey.
-Get him in the fucking car.
-Arno.
Get him in the car.
Go, go, come on,
let's get outta here. Go, go.
You fucking made me run,
you motherf--
[men clamoring]
Arno, what is happening?
Don't "Arno" me,
don't fucking say my name.
-[man] Give me the--
-Give me the keys.
The fucking Jew bit me.
Arno, hey, hey.
What's happening right now?
I told you how things were gonna go
if you didn't start to behave.
What? How was I not behaving?
Explain to me, I'm sorry--
I think I was very explicit on the phone
about how things were gonna go.
-Like the way things are going now?
-Give me the fucking keys to your car.
-What are you gonna do?
-[Phil] Give me the key.
Have 'em steal my Mercedes?
[Phil] Look what the fuck you did,
you fucking bit me.
Arno. Arno, fucking talk to me.
-Hello, Arno.
-Don't listen to him. It's not a game.
Stop saying my fucking name.
I have every intention of paying you back.
I'm broke right now.
You're broke? What's that, motherfucker?
-[Phil] Do you remember that?
-Look at it.
-Does that look familiar?
-That is money that's not mine.
That I sent to you because I wanted
to calm you down because--
We know for a fact that you placed a bet
with that money.
I never placed a bet with that money.
-[Arno] Yes, you did.
-No, I didn't.
[Arno] Let me ask you something.
I heard Beni and Eddie
are going to Timberlake.
Know what else I heard?
I heard you've resurfaced
your fucking swimming pool.
-I...
-Know how that makes me feel?
-...never resurfaced anything.
-You think your life is
-more important than--
-I don't know who said that.
[Phil] Give me the keys.
Shut the fuck up. Give me the keys
to your fucking car. Now!
Have the fucking keys. Fine.
All right, listen,
I do, I did, I admit it.
I... I... I made a bet, and guess what?
Here's the thing, I hit.
I hit the bet big.
-Okay?
-[Arno] You think I'm stupid?
You think I'm stupid, Howard.
You and your whole fucking family.
I'll call the book now.
Get on the phone with him, he'll tell you.
I saw the bookie.
You're talking about Gary?
You spoke to Gary about what?
-About what?
-About you.
About how you're taking my money
all over town, placing bets.
You know what that does to me,
you know how offensive that is to me?
What? You stopped the bet?
What do you think, asshole?
-You stopped the bet?
-Shut the fuck up.
[groans]
Congratulations, Arno,
you fucked ourselves outta money.
You fucked us both.
-[indistinct shouting]
-[choking]
-Take his clothes off.
-That fucking--
-[Phil] God, you gonna blame everybody.
-Gimme that fucking bracelet.
Hey, what's this? What's this?
-[Howard] It's not mine.
-This is more than my car.
-[Buddy] Hold this, motherfucker.
-Howard, you did this to yourself.
[Buddy] Take his fucking pants.
Take the fucking pants.
You're not getting a goddamn...
I gotta get to the auctioneers
next fucking week.
Give me my glasses.
I need my fucking glasses.
-[Buddy] Shut the fuck up.
-[Howard shouting]
Pull up up here. Come on, let's go.
Let me explain something to you,
motherfucker. Monday, I want the money.
Arno gets the money. All right?
I'm not fucking around anymore.
[Howard] My phone.
-[Phil] You hear me?
-Get him out of the car.
[Buddy] Get the fuck out the fucking car.
[Phil] Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Get in the fucking car.
Arno, Arno. Arno. All right.
Arno, listen to me.
-[Phil] Get in the car!
-Arno, Arno. Take the opal.
-[Buddy] Get in the fucking car.
-[Phil] Don't worry about it. Get in.
No, I want the underwear.
-[Phil] Take his underwear.
-No, no.
[Phil] Give me that.
-Give me your fucking underwear.
-No, no, no.
[Buddy] Give me the underwear,
you cocksucker.
Let that fucker rot in there.
Fuck you, Arno,
you cock-sucking motherfucker!
[car driving away]
Help. Help, help, help.
All right, you fuck.
[panting]
-[line ringing]
-Please, please, please.
Please pick up. Pick up the phone.
What is happening? [grunts]
Come on, come on.
[Dinah] Where are you?
Marcel's about to go on stage.
-Dinah...
-What do you want?
I locked... I locked my keys
in the trunk of the car.
Can you please... Can you come
to the parking lot and open it for me?
Fucking shit.
[car beeps]
It's okay. Thank you. Okay.
Sorry. I'll meet you right back inside.
It's all good now.
Let me get dressed.
[panting]
What could you possibly
be looking for in the forest
dressed in such thin paper rags?
[girl] My wicked stepmother
has condemned me to die
lest I fill this basket with roses
before the coming of dawn.
[boy] Besides our cottage
is our magic garden.
It protects the roses from the snow.
Go now and fill your basket
to your heart's content.
Dad, what the fuck?
Just watch your fucking sister.
It's fine.
[girl] Thank you, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
[laughter]
[boy] We must bestow a gift upon her.
I know. Every time she speaks,
gold coins shall spill forth
from her mouth.
This will be our gift.
[boy 2] Quick, he approaches now.
[Eiline whispers] This is
Danny's part, he's coming out.
[Danny] Hark, who goes there?
[Eiline whispers] He did so good.
[audience exclaiming in awe]
Wow.
-Fuck. Jesus Christ.
-[line ringing]
-[Demany on phone] Hello.
-Hey. Oh, you picked up, huh?
When I blocked the call, you pick up?
When you know it's me, you don't?
What was that all about?
Ah, I knew it was you calling, all right?
That's why I picked up.
Hey, where is my fucking gem?
Hey, hey, you need to calm down,
all right, I just happen to--
Listen, motherfucker. I want
my fucking property, you understand me?
Hey, watch your mouth. All right? You're
not dealing with some broke-ass nigga.
Hey, you fucking put me
on that bus ride home.
You think that was funny?
What the fuck was that all about?
That fucking bus was disgusting.
What the fuck you want me to do, huh?
I go into a locker room
with your silly ass,
it makes me look
really fucking suspect.
Where's my gem? Where is it?
I'm trying to help you,
not fuck everything up.
Jesus Christ, I have it on me right now.
You have it on you?
Yes, I'm about to be back in the city.
Okay, are you going to this fucking
Weeknd thing tonight?
I mean, I wasn't planning on it,
but I could.
You could? No, it's not you could.
You will, you'll meet me there.
It smells good.
What is it, barbecue chicken?
So, I wanted to talk
about the trunk scenario.
[Marcel] No, that was literally
the most awkward thing, like--
Where are you going?
I'm heading into the city.
Late night event. Gonna go...
This a cake?
...till 2:00, 3:00, you never know
anymore. So I'll be exhausted tomorrow.
Yeah, okay, sure.
[timer beeps]
Good night.
Anyway, I'll finish
the conversation later.
But it was literally so awkward. Like...
Who are you talking to?
Jessica.
Hi, Jessica.
How good was our girl tonight?
You can't hear her.
Okay, well, then just
hang up for a second.
Let me... Let me talk to you.
Two secs.
I'll call you back.
What?
So, I just, I was very proud of you
tonight. You were beyond incredible.
You told me like five times already.
Well, I just wanted... You really,
really to know how proud I was.
Okay? So I really...
I just really, really want you to know.
Okay, well, I do.
-Everything is cool, right?
-What do you mean?
I dunno, I just thought
I would check in with you.
Okay.
Make sure everything's good.
Why wouldn't I be good?
I don't know, I just thought I'd check in.
Okay, well, I literally don't know
what you're talking about, so...
That's right, 'cause I'm an idiot.
So you love me.
Okay, I'm gonna get into the city.
-Yeah, I'll see you in the morning.
-Have fun.
Like I always do.
[Marcel] Anyway, where was I?
You know, I have, like,
a complete resting bitch face. So...
-["Amen" by Meek Mill playing]
- I just wanna thank God
For all the pretty women
He let into my life
Wealth and health
For my family
And lettin' me ball on these niggas
There's a lot of bad bitches
In the building, Amen
A couple real niggas in the building
Demany, wait. I didn't see you out front,
I don't fucking see you in here now.
I can't believe I'm still looking for you.
Just, uh, pick up
your fucking phone, man.
I don't understand this.
You better fucking be here.
[man] Hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up.
Stop the music. Stop!
-[music stops]
-[crowd whines]
Yo, someone pass The Weeknd the mic.
[low synth intro playing]
[The Weeknd] Where the fuck's
the black light?
-[man] What's going on back there?
-No, I asked for a black light.
I'm not performing until there's a fucking
black light on this fucking stage.
[man] Put on the black light!
[crowd chanting] Black light, black light.
[man] Y'all not gonna hear The Weeknd
till you throw on the black light.
-[crowd] Black light, black light.
-[The Weeknd] Black light.
-[man] What's going on back there?
[crowd] Black light, black light,
black light, black light, black light,
black light, black light, black light...
[man] That's what I'm talking about.
["The Morning" playing]
[singing]  From the morning
Into the evening
Complaints from the tenants
Got the walls kicking
Like they six months pregnant
Drinking Aliz
With our cereal for breakfast
Girls calling cabs...
[Howard] Hey. Hey.
Demany.
Demany. Demany.
Howard, look.
Hey, I want you to meet my nigga, Jay.
Oh, yeah, you the guy.
I've been hearing about you.
Yo, where's that opal?
Gold all in chain, nigga, nigga, nigga
Gold all in my chain
Ey, you gonna ice me up?
Yeah, give me the opal.
[Demany] I don't have it.
I got you. Come by the shop any time,
he'll tell you where.
What'd you say? Where is it?
I'm sorry. I don't have it.
Whoa, whoa, you don't have it?
What do you mean?
-KG got it. I don't have it.
-KG has it?
What are you talking about?
You said on the phone you have it.
-Hey, change, I don't want that shit.
-That's why I fucking came here.
Why the fuck are you here
if you don't have the opal?
Same fucking reason everybody else here,
see The fucking Weeknd perform.
-That is The Weeknd.
-You got a problem with that?
-I got a very big problem with that, man.
-Whoa. Hey, hey.
[Howard] We came here for one
fucking reason, to get that--
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Calm your ass down.
Fuck you think this is?
-You good?
-I'm good. I'm good.
Give me that fucking drink.
I push it for the pleasure
Like a virgin to the game
A virgin to that money
A virgin to the fame
So this my only chance
And when I'm over only pray
That I flow from the bottom
Closer to the top
The higher that I climb
The harder I'ma drop
These pussy-ass niggas
Tryna hold on to their credit...
-Go fuck yourself.
-Hey, fuck you, nigga.
I said, why these niggas testing?
Always fucking testing
Why these niggas testing?
Shit that I got them on
Straight bar hoppin'
To the music of the ambiance
Get shit poppin'
Zombies of the night
Niggas ain't talkin'
If they hypin' to the crew
Get it in like
Downtown lovin'
When the moon comin'
Only place to find baseheads
And hot women
[sniffing]
There's some on your face.
-I don't even care.
-Is it off?
Yeah, I got it.
[Julia] Mm-mm.
-What are you doing?
-Need to enjoy. What are you doing?
-No touching. No touching.
-[muffled music thumping]
I wanna fuck you so bad.
-How bad?
-[sighs]
-I'll show you.
-Mm-mm.
-I said no touching.
-[The Weeknd] Feel the shit. Feel this.
Oh, my God. How are you even
this hard right now?
-[man] No...
-Whoa, slow down. Where you going?
Um, I was already inside.
Listen, I don't remember
seeing you inside.
Friends with The Weeknd.
-He told me to come after his set.
-If you're friends with somebody...
Hey, Flawless!
Watch the yelling.
Stop screaming over here.
Yo! Yo!
-Yo. Use the phone.
-Tell this guy to let me in! Come here!
[Flawless] The legend is in
the motherfucking building.
Come here, he's not letting me through.
Let him in. Sorry, man.
He's with me. Yeah, that's my guy.
What's up, sexy? How we doing?
Hey, check this out.
You seen this Rolls Royce
that I did? In Miami?
Yeah. Ritchie showed me that poison shit.
Where's Julia? She in there?
-Yeah, she's back there somewhere.
-With who?
You know what's going on
with my Michael Jackson pendant?
[Howard] What about that?
What do you mean? I need it back.
-It's in my safe.
-I'm coming by tomorrow to pick it up.
She's helping me sell this thing
to The Weeknd.
-You understand?
-[Howard] Yeah.
-[Flawless] I need you to help me.
-Where... Where is she? You know?
Yeah.
Well, where?
Where, where, where?
I don't mean to get in your business,
I don't wanna get involved,
but I saw her go to the bathroom
with The Weeknd.
Julia?
-Oh, shit.
-[Howard] Are you in there?
[The Weeknd] I said hold the door, bro.
-[Howard] Open up the door.
-[man] Yo. No one's in there.
Shut the fuck up!
[Julia] One second?
I'm washing my hands.
-Open up!
-Jesus.
Howard, we were just doing coke.
Nothing happened.
[all clamoring]
Get off of him!
Howard, get off of him!
[indistinct shouting]
Motherfucker!
Stop, guys!
[The Weeknd] Get the fuck back. Pussy!
Fuck you!
Fuck that motherfucker right there.
Fuck that bitch. Shut the fuck up.
I'm so sorry, Howard.
I'm so fucking sorry.
Hey, fuck you!
[man] Let's go. Get the fuck out.
You tell the fucking guy he's sued.
[Julia] I'm never coming back here again!
Howard, Howard! Howard!
Not one fucking DJ's gonna play his shit!
I know every fucking DJ in this town.
Fuck all you losers!
Howard?
[Howard] You smell like
his fucking cologne.
We didn't do anything, Howard!
-Yeah, right, right. Fucking...
-Howard...
[muttering angrily] Washing my fucking...
You blew a huge fucking sale for me!
What were you selling,
your fucking hot snatch?
Oh, my God!
Throwing my whole fucking life away
for this skank over here.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Now I'm a fucking skank.
Where the fuck are you?
Listen, Howard. You knew
what the fuck it was when you met me.
-That's right.
-Okay?
Yeah, that's why I wish
I'd never fucking met you. Right here.
Oh, wow. That's great, Howard. Howard!
-Get out of my fucking way.
-Howard. Howard.
Go fuck The Weeknd, all right?
-We didn't fucking do anything!
-Get the fuck off of me.
Go, go. Bye. Go.
Good night, bye. Get the fuck away.
-Howard.
-Go.
Howard. Howard.
-[driver] Lady, come on.
-[horn blares]
-Get out of the fucking car.
-Get out of the fucking way.
Get the fuck out of the way.
What are you gonna do, Howard?
What are you gonna do, big tough guy?
-I didn't fucking do anything with him.
-Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck away. Go fuck the guy.
Fuck you, Howard! I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow, Howard.
Yeah, fuck you.
[Howard] Let's go, go, go. Fuck you.
[choral music playing]
What the fuck are you looking at?
[woman] Oh, ho, ho, you got the...
Oh, funny. Stupid bitch.
That's why you're in line
in the fucking cold.
-[woman exclaims]
-Yeah, broke bitch.
[choral music continues]
[object clatters]
[aquarium water bubbling]
[sighs]
-[Howard] No, no.
-[Anne on phone] Howard.
-No, listen, Anne.
-Howard.
-[machine whirring loudly]
-I'm looking at the opal.
-You are missing the point.
-I'm looking at it right now.
-It's gorgeous.
-It is not you...
-It's just...
-...who should be looking at it, it's me.
Turn that down.
-Let me explain something to you.
-What?
Your opal is one of 75 items
I have to open in this auction.
Uh... Uh, listen...
All of them but yours have been cleaned,
cataloged and appraised.
I'm doing some appraisals of my own, okay.
[phone ringing]
And then I'm gonna
bring it to you today.
I'm on the precipice
of pulling it right now.
I swear to you, please.
-End of the day or we're done.
-I'm getting a call right now...
-End of the day, Howard, I'm serious.
-...so I have to go.
This is Howard Ratner.
-[Janet] How are you?
-Thank you so much
for calling me back so quickly.
Yeah, no problem. That message you left,
actually was very disturbing.
No, no, I didn't mean to worry you.
-Mind telling me what this is about?
-[phone ringing]
I saw online that your boss
represents Kevin Garnett.
I'm gonna have to put you on hold.
One moment.
Okay, sure, sure, I'll hang on.
[woman] Howard, Julia's on line one.
No. No. Tell her no.
I'm not here. Fuck it.
[buttons beep]
Where are you?
[Julia] Why aren't you
answering your phone?
I asked you a question. Where are you?
I stayed at Kat's house.
Where else do you think?
I couldn't fucking go home
with you acting that way.
No. No. That's... So let me guess,
you're not coming to work today?
I would like to.
That must be nice to come to work
whenever you feel like it.
Oh, Howard.
Is that... Is that good? Is that good?
Maybe you should take a nap, then.
-Take a nap, get your rest.
-Can we please talk this out?
-You're being a baby right now.
-You need to remain attractive, right?
Answer me.
I just wanna sit down
-and talk to you, Howard.
-Okay.
I don't wanna do this.
I don't wanna fight.
-And I just need to work, okay?
-[phone ringing]
I need to work to make sure
that your cheating ass is taken care of.
[Joani] Howard, personnel on line two.
-[Howard] Goodbye.
-[buttons beep]
This is Howard Ratner.
[woman] My assistant told me
that you called? How are you doing?
I'm not gonna lie to you,
I could be better.
Sorry to hear that. What can I do for you?
I've been having a situation
with one of your higher-profile players,
and I'm moments away right now
from making things very ugly for you.
-Okay. Can you hang on for a second?
-No, I'm not hanging on.
-I happen to be a litigious individual.
-Mmm.
And I am a second away
from hanging up right now
-and calling my lawyer and the police...
-Whoa, whoa.
-[doorbell]
-[Joani] Howard, KG is here with Demany.
I have no idea what you're talking about,
you're starting to sound like an asshole,
so maybe you wanna back up--
-[buzzer sounds]
-Never mind.
Kevin.
-Hey. Hey.
-[indistinct chatter]
[buzzer sounds]
-What's up?
-Buzz the man in.
-[Demany] Hey, buzz us in.
-[buzzer sounding]
-[Howard] Wow. Buzz.
-I am. I am, Howard.
Buzz the fucking door.
Go to the other buzzer, please. Hurry up.
[man] Try one more time.
-[Howard] Right there, go ahead.
-[buzzer sounding]
It's not working. Howard.
God damn it. God damn it.
-Hang on, sorry.
-Open this shit up.
I'm sorry.
We don't got time for this.
He got a game tonight.
The magnet sometimes doesn't connect.
You brought the gem?
-I'm claustrophobic.
-[KG] I got the gem right here.
[Howard] Good. There it is.
-We're gonna go downstairs and wait.
-You can't leave
-because that one's locked off.
-We'll wait downstairs.
-Open up.
-Get a fucking hammer.
-What's going on, man?
-Roman. He needs a hammer.
-[Howard] We'll be right there.
-Let me get a hammer.
[Howard] I, honestly,
it's gonna be a second.
Move it! Give me the fucking...
Give me the hammer.
I'm on it. I'm coming.
This usually works. This'll work.
Give me this.
-[KG] Man.
-And get ready to buzz, okay?
-Ow!
-[Demany] Oh, my God.
-Sorry, buzz, buzz.
-[buzzer sounding]
-Shit loud as a bitch.
-Are you fucking kidding me?
[doorbell chimes]
Buzz. Hit it from the side...
[Joani] Flawless is here.
[Howard] Get rid of this motherfucker.
Tell him goodbye.
-Oh, my God, Flawless is here?
-We ain't got time for this.
-Goodbye to fucking Flawless. Roman!
-[Joani] It's not working, I can't...
-What?
-[Howard] Come out here.
Oh, shit.
[Howard] We're having
a fucking connection issue.
Just get me some fucking metal shavings
and the tool fucking kit, all right?
God damn it.
I'm going to get this open,
I promise you this will work.
-Hurry the fuck up, Roman. Thank you.
-[Roman] Relax.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-[Demany] Slow bastard.
-I'm here to buy the opal.
-[Howard] I... I...
-It's game day for me.
-[Howard] I know it is.
-[KG] What the fuck is going on?
-Listen to me.
I got $175,000 in this bag.
170... I told you this thing's
worth over a million dollars.
[Demany] Come on, man.
What the fuck you doing?
-[Howard] I saw...
-Four courtside seats.
I live in New York. I don't know
what that's going to do to me.
KG, I wanna give it to you for free.
I'm that kinda guy.
Just, I'm tied into an auction right now.
What you talk-- What auction?
-The auction?
-[KG] Yeah.
Listen, make a bid.
Make a bid at the auction.
-[KG] When is it? When?
-It's Monday.
-Monday.
-[Demany] D'ah...
-Tell him to come--
-Let him rent it a couple nights.
I'll hold it till Monday,
you get it back Monday night.
It's perfect, and you know it.
[Howard] Kevin, I hate
letting you down like this.
This motherfucker says no
to everything! Say yes to something!
I want to, Kevin. I fucking love you.
I feel like an asshole, believe me.
-[KG] You are.
-[Demany] Howard.
Come down, let me fucking do this.
Jesus, fucking, I got this.
God fucking damn it,
-I gotta do everything.
-[knocking on door]
Please, stop knocking.
It's not gonna help.
-Go, go.
-[buzzer sounding]
KG, I'm so goddamn sorry.
-[Demany] Jesus Christ, man.
-I'm so sorry.
Got a door don't work.
What's going on here, man?
Get them some waters,
get the cold waters.
We don't need any water.
Go get my ring
so I can get up out of here.
Get him his fucking ring.
He got shit to do.
-The ring. The ring. The ring.
-[KG] Yeah. My ring. My ring.
[Demany] He's got a game,
get him the ring.
The ring. Oh, my God, no.
I left the fucking ring in Long Island.
What the fuck do you mean
you left it in Long--
-[groans]
-I'll give it to Demany.
[KG] I don't have time for this.
[Howard] I'll get it to Demany.
[Howard] No, I'll give it to you.
I need the stone.
I don't-- Listen, I can't do this.
I don't have confidence.
You don't have to do-- I know,
but I need the stone.
-[KG] Do me a favor, you need the stone?
-Yeah.
Where's my ring at though?
I'll get you the ring.
I'm gonna give it to Demany.
-[KG] Do me a favor.
-He'll give it to you...
[KG] Get my ring for me.
I'll see you later.
-He'll go to Boston...
-[KG] Howard, this is bullshit.
[Howard] It's... I apolo...
-[man] Open this fucking door, y'all.
-[KG] Why we come up here, man?
-Yo, buzz us out, Howard.
-We'll buzz you out.
-Please buzz him out.
-[KG] This is crazy.
KG, forgive me for everything I did
and the time I wasted and you...
Fucking asshole. You fucking did this!
-Yo.
-You. What have you been telling him?
What the fuck
are you talking about, Howard?
Look, this is how this shit works.
I bring niggas here to you to buy jewelry.
That's how I get fucking paid.
[Howard] Got a lot of nerve
talking to me right now.
-Fuck are you talking about?
-That fiasco you caused.
The nigga just offered you
a quarter of a million dollars
for a fucking rock, dummy.
That's all me.
-My shit. Yes.
-'Cause of you?
-I had nothing to do with it.
-That's 20 grand...
You spoke to those guys in Ethiopia?
You put all the calls in?
-Yeah, my bad.
-Fuck you.
Taking all my niggas somewhere.
Where my shit at?
-[safe thudding]
-What the fuck? Get outta there.
[Demany] Where's my shit? There's
only three fucking watches in here.
-I don't want you in there.
-Where's the rest of my shit?
Where my watches at? There's three.
-I loaned them.
-What do you mean you loaned them?
[Howard] These are fake Rollies, so what?
-They're $200.
-Nigga, that's my shit.
Nigga, them boxes is mad expensive,
you fucking idiot.
Well, I owe you, then.
Get outta there I said.
Fuck you, get the fuck off of me, man.
[Joani] I have Dr. Blauman on line one.
The fuck is my shit?
-Go ahead. Go ahead. Hi.
-[Dr. Blauman] Howard?
-Hi, Doctor. What's going on?
-[Demany] Where's my shit?
-[Dr. Blauman] Howard.
-[Howard] Yes.
-Where's the papers?
-[Howard] Please be quiet.
-Is everything okay?
-Yeah.
-Where's the fucking papers?
-Shut the fuck up.
-[Demany] Bitch ass.
-Howard? Me?
-[Howard] Go ahead, I'm sorry.
-Man, this...
-Howard, um... Uh...
-[Howard] What do I got?
[Demany] Fuck is this?
...the results of your colonoscopy,
so we're good. You're all good.
-Everything came back clean.
-Bitch-ass motherfucker.
Fuck you
and that goddamn phone call, nigga.
So it's clean 100%? You said it's good?
-Yeah, I said you're all clean.
-Good. Thank you. That's a relief.
-Howard, relax. This is just routine.
-You ain't even listening to me, my nigga.
[Howard] My father died from it,
so of course.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
But you know, given your family history.
-I know, I know.
-Something you gotta take seriously.
Jews and colon cancer. What is that?
I thought we were the chosen people?
Colon cancer just paid
for my house in the Hamptons.
[Howard] Don't tell me, where?
What part of the Hamptons?
How many acres?
[Roman] Whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
You're gonna kill the fish.
What the fuck? My fish.
Howard?
My fish! My fish, you fuck.
You get a glass, get a glass.
-Fuck them goddamn fish, nigga.
-What the fuck are you doing?
You fucking asshole.
Get a fucking another glass.
Get another glass. God damn it.
-[buzzer sounds]
-Come here. I got you, cocksucker.
There you go, there you go.
I got you, sweetheart.
-Joani...
-[Dr. Blauman] Howard.
[Howard] Joani,
please get some more glasses.
[Tony] Can't see the water. They're blind.
[Dr. Blauman] Howard, I'm hanging up.
[buzzer sounds]
[Anne on phone] I thought I was clear,
at 5:30 I am out of the door.
I told you I was coming to you.
I'm coming to you.
-I have the stone.
-I have a train.
-Don't leave.
-I have a wedding in Newport.
-Howard. Howard, I--
-No.
Howard. Howard, stop.
You're being fucking crazy again. Stop.
Listen, I got no time to talk.
I have to be at Adley's in 15 minutes
before they close.
I'll go with you.
[Howard] Then I gotta get
to my father-in-law.
-Please.
-That's enough.
I'm really sick, I don't feel well.
I got out of bed to come see you.
-I see you were in a big rush?
-[Julia] I was in a really big rush.
-You got yourself a fucking smoothie.
-[gasps] I was in a big rush.
-I want you out.
-You motherfucker!
You're out of the apartment
by the end of the day.
-Fuck you.
-[cup clatters]
[Howard] Out of my life.
You have no idea with this.
-How you doing, Howie?
-[Howard] All right.
Hey. Good Pesach, Howard.
All right, Larry.
You're a Jew again? Welcome back.
Have a good Pesach. It's all right.
-[man] Hey, Howard.
-[Howard] Hey.
[reciting prayer in Hebrew]
[all speak Hebrew]
Dip the celery?
[all crunching]
[cell phone vibrates]
[man] You know who kinda
sucks schmeck a little bit?
Overrated? Chris Paul.
[man 2] Quit playing, man,
he's all NBA. I mean, he can't do it.
[Gooey] Noah. Eddie?
Please, that's enough.
[man] You don't know anything.
What are you saying?
-Shut up, everybody.
-[man] All right, all right.
-[woman] Shh. Please.
-Natalie, Natalie, you're up.
[Natalie] Wait, you skipped my dad.
Uh, where are we?
Howie, why don't you read
the, um, plagues.
Okay.
Uh, Ma, you, uh, take the Hebrew
and I'll take the English.
Yes, my dear.
Here we go.
[Howard's mom reading plagues
in Hebrew]
[Howard in English] Okay, blood.
-[reading in Hebrew]
-[in English] Frogs.
-[in English] Lice.
-[reading in Hebrew]
-[in English] Wild animals.
-[in English] Pestilence.
-[reading in Hebrew]
-[in English] Boils.
-[in English] Hail.
-[reading in Hebrew]
-[in English] Locusts.
[reading in Hebrew]
[in English] Darkness.
-[reading in Hebrew]
-[in English] Death of the first born.
Hard core back there.
-[laughter]
-Ah, that can still happen.
You know, watch yourselves, kids.
[line rings]
[on voicemail] Hey, it's Julia.
Please don't leave me a message,
-I don't check this, text me.
-Excuse me.
-[line beeps]
-You send me something like that
and then you don't pick up
your phone?
Are you... You fucking with me?
I'm trying to have a nice peaceful dinner
with my family,
which is something you wouldn't understand
because you don't have one.
You wanna play mind games with me? Huh?
So whatever you meant
by your little link,
I meant when I said I want you
out of my apartment tonight.
And I want confirmation by text.
Not a link.
Via text: "Howie, I am gone."
10:00 pm. Don't you fucking call me.
[indistinct chatter]
Arno, what the fuck?
Can we just fucking talk?
We're family, we're here right now.
Get outta my way.
Yeah? You're not so tough
without your friends around, are you?
Are you? Are you? Fucking pussy.
[man 1] Oh, you like...
You love this roster?
-[man 2] I love it. But that...
-[man 1] Baron Davis is done.
[man 2] Start fresh. 'Melo. Amar'e...
-What about Lin?
-That's it.
We gotta bring back Lin.
You know why fucking, uh,
Lin's not coming back next year?
'Cause Dolan saw everybody was
so fucking happy.
-He thought, "How can I ruin that?"
-[man] Exactly! Howard knows. On top of...
You realize that I met my wife
at the first game that started Linsanity.
-Know what he says to me?
-Hmm?
He comes over to me and says...
"Happy holidays." Like it's Christmas.
It's like having an intruder
in your own home.
[man] And we'll never live it down.
He's not bothering anybody
though, right? He's trying.
[Gooey] Yeah, easy for you to say.
He didn't marry your daughter. Shh.
[man] You know who sells the vitamins
on Amazon, he's got the lisp.
[Howard] Here he is.
All good.
[man 1] ...got the sprained ankle,
so, the guy's a schmuck.
[man 2] Man, KG wouldn't even dare
mess with Amar'e or 'Melo, man.
[Eddie] I drafted Darren
and I got Winston.
[Gooey] This is, uh, KG, huh?
-[Howard] Oh. Three for 11? What the fuck?
-Yeah, he looks tortured.
That fucking guy tried
to steal an opal from me.
Your opal came?
-The opal came, yeah.
-Yeah?
Yeah. Stupidly I lent it
to this motherfucker.
No. What do you mean,
he took it? He stole it?
He didn't steal it. He got carried away.
He thinks it has magic powers.
Magic powers?
[laughing]
No, really?
[Howard] Yeah. Look at him tonight.
Without it.
He didn't have it tonight,
look how fucking bad he played.
He wants to own it.
So I tell him, "Come to the auction,
fucking make a bid for it,
like everyone else."
-[Gooey] So, when is this auction?
-[Howard] The auction is Monday.
[Gooey] Uh-huh.
Okay, so what do you think it's worth?
Well, listen, it's anywhere
from 1,000 to $3,000 a carat.
And it's 600 carats.
[exclaims] That's over
a million dollars. He's rich.
-[Howard] Not as rich as Gooey, but...
-[Gooey laughing]
I'm working on that.
That's a hard place...
Who's comparing? Rich is rich.
I made a crazy risk, a gamble,
and it's about to pay off.
[Gooey] Oh, man.
[children chattering playfully]
Uh-uh-uh. Don't look at us,
don't look at him,
don't look at me, find it yourself.
Come on, keep looking.
Now warm, warm, warm, warmer.
Very warm.
Keep looking. Keep looking.
-I found it.
-[all cheering]
Yeah!
That's my boy.
[speaks Hebrew]
-[Howard's mom] Oh, my God.
-Find your stuff. We're leaving soon.
[Howard's mom]
I can't believe. So nice. Listen...
[Marcel] It'll fit. It looks so good.
[Howard's mom] Let's show Daddy.
Dad, look. This is Mom's bat mitzvah
dress. It still fits her.
Let's show Grandpa.
[Howard] Ah! It's hysterical.
Hey. It's nine o'clock.
What do you think? Shall we get going?
-Yeah, let's go tell the boys.
-I told them, I told them.
-What?
-Um...
-You look gorgeous.
-Oh, God.
I wanted to talk to you for a minute.
Just sit down
and we don't have to do it here.
We'll wait, but I, uh...
I'm having very serious
second thoughts, and, uh...
we're all together right now,
we're all so comfortable. It's...
Is it too late? Should we maybe?
What do you think? Am I crazy?
Are you serious right now?
Yeah. I know,
I know I fucked up. I know I did.
You fucked up. You are a fuck-up.
I'm not having this conversation.
Please stop. Just stop for one second
and just look at me.
Look in my eyes. And they'll tell you
what I'm feeling.
-Please, please.
-[sighs heavily]
-[laughing]
-What?
-What are you thinking?
-[laughing]
-What? Tell me, tell me, I wanna...
-Oh, my God.
I know. What?
Your face is so stupid.
-Stupid.
-[Howard] Okay.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna leave her.
I'll leave her. I don't need her.
We're done.
-It's done.
-Okay. Okay.
It was stupid. She's trash.
She's trash. I know that.
I was stupid. I'm done. I'm done.
It means nothing. Meant nothing.
Please. I'm begging you,
just give me another shot.
-You know what, Howard?
-Say yes. What?
I think you are the most
annoying person I have ever met.
I hate being with you,
I hate looking at you.
And if I had my way,
I would never see you again.
That's 'cause you're mad.
You're mad and it makes sense.
-You can punch me if you want.
-Oh, thanks.
-Hey, I was ready for that.
-[laughs]
[overlapping chatter]
I don't even want to touch you.
[woman] Oh, my God.
Are you kidding me?
-[woman 2] Wait, turn around.
-Did you see that?
Oh, my God, I hate you.
Does that fit you right now?
-I'm 15 pounds overweight.
-I hate you right now.
I'll get the car. Okay? I'll get the car.
[woman] Oh, my God!
You look so good.
[man on radio] New York
and Long Island's home of classic rock.
Q106.7, The Rock.
She's always-- Like we wanna see
everything she's doing at every moment.
-You think she's jealous of me?
-[Marcel] Yeah, she wants your life.
-She wants our house.
-[Dinah] She can have it.
[Eddie] Look at the way
you're playing. Pull right.
Why are you taking Lex?
Take the tunnel,
it's better, less traffic.
[Eddie] Let me focus. Give me the phone.
Plus, I wanna grab something
from the apartment, it's right there.
[Eddie] Go left, go left.
-Hit the boss.
-[Beni laughs] I hit him.
Gonna stop by the apartment, guys.
-[Eddie] Oh, my God.
-[Beni] Come on, Mom.
[Dinah] Daddy's got things to do.
[Eddie] Wow, so annoying.
[Dinah] Got business.
["The Stranger" by Billy Joel playing]
[Eddie] You died!
Well, we all have a face
That we hide away forever
And we take them out
And show ourselves...
-Hi, Mr. Ratner, how are you?
-How are you?
Anything in the trunk?
[Dinah] Eddie's got to go to the bathroom.
-I gotta use the bathroom.
-Just... hold it in, all right?
-It's 25 minutes, we're home.
-I can't wait that long.
Don't be ridiculous.
Eddie, go upstairs and use the bathroom.
[Howard] I'm tired, I wanna go to sleep.
Couldn't go at Grandpa's?
You had to wait till now?
Come on. We're going, we're going.
God damn it.
Bathroom's all fucked up
because of construction,
so I'm gonna ask the neighbor if...
I don't wanna use a neighbor's bathroom,
I'm taking a shit.
-You ever see this show Good Times?
-No.
You're actually gonna like this.
This guy was the father on the show.
-[knocks on door]
-What? I don't care.
[Howard] I showed it to you.
["Rain" by Madonna
playing on speakers]
He was in Coming to America.
[Eddie] Probably sleeping.
Bet you he's a old man.
[man] Who is it?
It's Howard next door. I live in E.
-Hey, how are you?
-What's up?
Unfortunately, my bathroom's
fucked up and this kid's gotta go.
Can we use yours for a minute?
No. Sorry.
[Eddie] What a fucking dickhead.
Hey, stop that. He's a fucking legend.
[knocks on door]
[man 2] Hello?
Hi. I'm, uh, your neighbor.
Hey, how you doing?
How are you? I'm your neighbor,
-I never introduced myself.
-Alan, how are you?
My bathroom's all fucked up
and my son needs to use,
can he use yours for a second?
What is it?
Number one, number two?
-Number one.
-He's gonna go one.
-So you go quick.
-All right, in the back.
[Howard] I'll meet you in the hallway.
["Rain" by Madonna continues playing]
Rain
Feel it on my fingertips
Hear it on my window pane
Your love's coming down like
- Rain
-Julia?
Wash away my sorrow
Take away my pain
Your love's coming down like
Rain
"Have a nice life. I hope you find
everything you're looking for."
Could you see my tears
[turns music off]
[doorbell rings]
Yeah. Hey, I'm coming.
[banging on door]
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go.
Who's the girl
living in your apartment?
What'd you say?
That guy told me there's some
hot chick living in your apartment.
Who's that? Mom?
What are you doing
talking to that cokehead?
-He was talking to me.
-I told you to go in and take a shit.
-I did take a shit.
-Get on the elevator.
It's enough already.
-[buttons clicking]
-Don't...
Don't talk about that to anybody.
Did you get what you needed?
Yeah.
[dogs barking]
[Dinah] Put the recycling and the garbage
out before you come in the house.
[garbage can rolling]
Down here...
It's a big day.
Magnolia Bakery
from the downtown. Original.
-You have these yet? Delicious.
-Thank you.
You tell everybody here, thank you so much
for everything they've done for me.
-[receptionist] Will do.
-These are on me, Howard Ratner.
And what's this?
This is the, uh, catalog for today?
That's the one.
If they want anybody else to come in,
they have to tell me beforehand.
-Stops right on me.
-Thank you.
[sniffs]
What the fuck is this? This is a mistake.
That's a correction.
No, it's a correction,
but it's a fucking mistake.
Where's Anne? I wanna speak with her.
I'm sorry,
Anne is in a meeting right now.
No. Get her out of the meeting.
It's an emergency. I wanna speak with her.
Call her on the phone, please. Thank you.
-If you promise to keep your voice down.
-Jesus. Yes.
I'm happy to call her.
Jesus fucking Christ.
[line ringing]
Hello, Anne?
I'm down here with Howard Ratner.
Ask how this fucking
155 bullshit happened?
Did you hear that? Mm-hmm. Okay.
What? What did she say?
-I'm afraid that's your appraisal.
-I know that's what it says.
I'm asking who came up
with the fucking figure?
Oscar in Gems.
Well, Oscar's fucking wrong.
I could go out and get
six appraisers right now,
five of them would say
at least $3,000 a carat.
He can go to six appraisers and...
Give me the phone.
Can I speak to her, please?
Can I speak with her?
I'm sorry,
I'm gonna have to hand you over.
[Anne] No, that won't be necessary.
I'd rather you didn't.
-Anne.
-Yes.
This is fucking outrageous.
You need to calm yourself down,
Mr. Ratner.
I don't wanna be calm.
This appraisal's a fucking joke.
Oscar happens to be one of our most
experienced gemologists
-who we were extremely lucky to get.
-Knows nothing about colored stones.
Why the fuck am I hearing
about it now? I mean...
Do I need to remind you that you brought
the opal to us on a Friday night
for an auction set on a Monday morning?
We were lucky to be able
-to get it appraised at all.
-I don't give a fuck.
I don't care.
It needs to be changed. Do it.
Well, that's not an option,
but if you like, we can pull it.
-Pull it? No. No. Not gonna pull it, okay?
-What?
Here's what you'll do.
You're gonna make an announcement
at the top of the auction
that the correction was wrong
-and the original estimate stands.
-No, no, no, no, no.
We are not correcting a correction.
We can either pull it, or carry on as is.
It's entirely up to you.
Okay, thank you so much.
-Okay, Anne. No, I'm sorry, too.
-I've bent over backwards for you.
-We are done here. I've had enough.
-That'll be perfect. I'll let her know.
Let who know? Me and my staff
had to work the entire weekend...
Okay. Thank you so much.
-I don't care what we make.
-From the bottom of my heart...
-I'm happy I won't have to work with you.
-...I apologize. I'll tell her.
-I can assure you...
-Thank you. Okay.
So she said that we, uh, need to,
uh, take the inserts out of each catalog
before the auction starts.
So, uh, you have those.
If you want, I saw a box down there
and I can start on these.
-What is that? What are you doing?
-I have a question for Anne.
You don't need to call her.
I just spoke with her.
A separate question, don't worry.
Howard.
Hi, Anne. He's saying
you told him it was...
Okay. Hey, listen, just fuck 'em.
Put 'em back in, I don't give a shit.
-Gooey!
-We're here.
-[Howard] You're a sight for sore eyes.
-Is he here?
Ah, KG? He is, uh...
I didn't see him yet.
-Is he here?
-I haven't seen him, but I...
-I got all these things for him to sign.
-Listen to me, listen. Do you want that?
-Get it before the auction starts. It's...
-[Aaron] I gotta...
Go to the auction room.
See if you can see him.
Find him in there.
[Howard] He's a great guy.
You'll love him.
-He's excited.
-So I wanna ask you a little favor, okay?
-Yeah, what? What favor?
-So, um... I need you to jack up the bids.
What? No, ab-- No.
No, absolutely not.
Gooey, a little bit. Here and there,
you make a bid for it.
I just gotta ensure we get it up to $250.
What if I win at $250?
That's easy.
I'll give it right back to you.
-But you're not gonna...
-Jesus!
[Howard] Hey.
This is not really a nice position
you put me in, you know? I resent this.
-Think I wanna do this?
-Very much.
I fucked up.
I should have got my own appraisal,
but I didn't have the time.
How much did they appraise it for?
-$200.
-$200?
-Yeah, but these assholes...
-What happened to one point--
...they don't have an opal specialist.
-My guy at the AGL says...
-$200?
...$500 just based off the pictures.
So, okay, listen.
20%, I'll give you for the winning bid.
To be a partner with me.
KG's gonna buy it. It's not a problem.
This guy's obsessed with the stone.
Today was supposed to be
about Aaron meeting KG. Hmm?
-Gooey.
-To show support.
That's what
today was supposed to be about.
Well, this is support, this is support
like you've never known.
-Sold to you. Thank you so much, sir.
-[applause]
We move on now, ladies and gentlemen,
to lot number 38.
Lot 38, we have a sale room notice.
I'm required to inform you all
that this fine Ethiopian black opal
presented here before you all
on your left, my right,
is now offered with a revised estimate
of $155 to $225,000 US.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is a fine piece, a collector's work,
and most importantly,
it is windowed on either side
to reveal the full spectrum
of its dazzling color
and the pin fire pattern within.
So, with that in mind,
ladies and gentlemen,
my colleagues are ready
and poised on the phones
and you're all ready with your paddles,
we shall start the bidding now at $20,000.
$20,000, $30,000.
Do I have $40,000?
$40,000, gentleman's bid.
Pleasure to see you, sir. Thank you, sir.
$40,000 now. Do I see 50?
$50,000 now, in a new place.
Thank you, sir.
Pleasure to have you back, too, sir.
$50,000 now against you, sir.
Shall we say 60?
$60,000 now against you, sir.
$70,000 now against you, sir.
-One hundred grand.
-[all gasp]
One hundred thousand
now bid with you, sir.
In a great place, a big bold giant leap
for a big, bold giant leaper.
At $100,000 now.
It's no longer yours, sir.
It's against you, sir.
Gonna try one more, sir?
I'll even break an increment for you, sir.
Can I urge you to consider
a bid of $105,000, sir?
Come on, sir, you sure?
Positive? No further? A defiant nod then.
Looking then for 110 in the room.
It's $100,000 now.
Is there any further bidding?
$110,000 now?
Welcome back, sir.
$110,000 now.
Once again, against you, sir.
Shall we try 120? 120 now.
Try one more, sir? Let's try 130?
130 now. Shall we try 140?
$140,000 now.
Come on, sir, let's up it again to 150.
Try one more at $150,000.
No longer yours, sir.
Shall we try 160? 160 now.
Back against you again, sir.
Can we try one more at 170?
170 now.
Say 180? Say 180, sir?
[whispers] We agreed on 175.
-[auctioneer] $180,000 now.
-It's fine.
[auctioneer] Bid back against you, sir.
I'm looking for $190,000.
$190,000 is bid. Against you, sir.
[whispers indistinctly]
[auctioneer] $190,000.
Confer with your advisor now.
-[KG] Are you serious?
-[Liz] I am serious.
[KG] It's okay. I need this stone.
Wanna move this up.
Any higher? Any further?
[KG] Relax. Relax.
[auctioneer] It's the last chance
for you, sir.
-[KG] Serious?
-[auctioneer] Move this along.
We have a good bid at $190,000.
I'm looking for 200, sir.
Gonna move this up.
Any higher, any further?
Sure, sir? Last chance.
-[whispers] Let's go.
-[auctioneer] Fair warning. With you, sir.
At $190,000, against the phones.
-[cell phone chimes]
-Against the rest of the room.
Sold to you, sir, at $190,000.
[applause]
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir. Paddle 172.
[elevator bell dings]
[Gooey] All right.
-Gooey. I'm so goddamn sorry.
-Shh.
-Thank you very much.
-You're welcome.
I'm sorry. Listen, I--
49th Street, I'm supposed
to be on 48th Street.
Thank you. Thank you.
It's 190 grand, Howard.
-190 grand.
-That's temporary.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I gotta tell you,
I was gonna stop past 200.
Did I not tell you that was gonna happen?
-I'm sorry.
-So now what?
Your money's gonna go into my account,
and I'll wire it right back to you.
-Like it never happened.
-Including 20%?
Absolutely. That comes
right out of my pocket.
That is nearly 38 grand, Howard.
-[Howard] I know that.
-That's 38 grand.
So I'm gonna need a couple of weeks
on that, but it'll be done.
-I promise you, okay?
-All right. Aaron, let's go.
-[Aaron] I got like six autographs.
-[Gooey] Now!
-[Howard] All right--
-See you, Gooey.
[Howard] You got the autographs?
That's great.
[Aaron] Yeah.
[Gooey] Great.
-[Howard] Wasn't Garnett a champ? Hey?
-[Aaron] Oh, yeah.
-[Howard] Don't be mad at me?
-Get in.
Please? Please don't be mad.
Come on. Can I get the opal?
Let me get the opal.
-What for?
-Because I gotta sell that.
-Take the fucking opal.
-Yes, all right.
-Thanks.
-[Gooey] Close the door.
Get 'em going.
Open the fucking door.
What's he waiting for you for?
Okay. All right.
I know, I know, I know. I know.
Let 'em go, let 'em go
and then we'll talk.
-The fuck was that?
-All right, I fucked up.
I fucked up, it was a mistake, all right?
I know. I admit it.
I gotta just... Let's hit pause
for one fucking second.
Gonna call Kevin 'cause I know
he fucking wants it.
And you saw he's got the 175 and then
everything will be copasetic.
All right?
KG. It's me.
I got great news for you. I--
Hello?
No one on the fucking phone.
-[cell phone clatters]
-If you just give me two fucking--
Shut the fuck up.
[choking]
[Phil] You're lucky there's people around.
Come on, get outta here. Let's go.
[stifled voice] Hey, fucking...
[choking]
[clearing throat]
Hey!
Arno, Arno.
Just listen to me, please.
I spoke to Demany, remember Demany?
He's a business friend of mine.
He gave me the fucking number...
That's enough, Howard!
That's fucking enough!
[Howard] Why are you being
so thick headed? I don't--
All right, fuck you, man. Suck my dick!
Throw him in the fucking water.
[Howard groans]
All right, let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Where the fuck are my glasses?
My fucking God, where are they?
[indistinct chatter]
Got the Versace...
-I don't know if this is a $400 bag.
-Mm-hmm.
[Julia] Maybe $250.
[man] Howard! There he is. Howard!
[man 2] Forget about Howard,
that Brioni's...
[breathing heavily]
[indistinct chatter]
[intercom beeps]
-[Joani] Howard, Joseph...
-I'm not feeling good.
-You okay? What's wrong?
-I don't... I don't wanna work.
Send everybody home.
All right, sweetie.
[indistinct chatter]
[knocking on door]
Hey. Sorry to bother you.
[Howard] What is it?
I just wanted to see
how the auction went.
[Howard] Terrible. I don't...
-I don't wanna talk about it.
-[Julia] Okay.
Well, Damian and Joseph
brought this amazing sweat suit
that I think would look so nice on you.
Do you wanna see it?
[Howard] Just leave me alone, please.
Come on, Howard.
Don't... Don't look at me.
Oh, my God, Howard.
-[tearfully] Don't look at me.
-What the fuck happened to you?
Don't look at me, please.
[sobbing]
I don't know if I can take it.
I don't know what everybody's...
Not ever going right.
[Julia] I know, I know.
I'm so sad. I'm so fucked up.
I'm so fucked up.
[tearfully] Yeah, I'm really upset too.
I'm sorry if this is anything
to do with me,
but I swear, I really didn't do anything.
I wish you were nicer to me though.
It was not nice what you did to me.
I try, but it's really hard.
I don't know what to do.
I don't have any place to go.
I don't have anywhere to get better.
But you do.
Like, really, Howard, you're my home.
You could come to me.
No, I don't-- I can't figure it out.
I can't figure out
what I'm supposed to do.
Everything I do is not going right.
I don't know what to do.
I really don't.
-I don't want any more of this shit.
-Yeah.
-I really don't. I gotta figure this out.
I gotta figure this out, I really do.
Well, I got something if you want.
But you can't make fun of me.
What?
[chuckles]
My God, it's so stupid, but...
I don't know... I got it, I thought...
I thought it would
make you feel better. [sniffles]
Look, unzip my skirt.
Not like that, just unzip my skirt.
[chuckles]
It says, "Howie."
What did you do?
Why would you do that?
[Julia] You don't like it?
[Howard] No, I do. I'm not worth it.
-Yes, you are worth it.
-I'm not worth it.
-Look, Howie, I'm so crazy about you.
-I don't deserve this.
Yes, you do. I love you.
-No, no, you gonna...
-[chuckling] Yeah.
You can't even get buried with me now.
-Oh, it's okay.
-[doorbell chimes]
Oh, this fucking guy.
Do not let him in. Understand me?
Just ignore him. Ignore him, Joani.
-[doorbell continues chiming]
-[intercom beeps]
[sniffles]
-Let's get you clean.
-[groans]
-[groaning]
-It's not broken, right?
You don't think it's broken, right?
This is crazy.
You can't be out here looking like this.
-[sniffles]
-[Julia clicks tongue] Aw.
[cell phone ringing]
Can you answer that?
Hello?
[on phone] Oh, hi, this is Liz,
I work with Kevin.
-I'm actually looking for Howard.
-This is Howard.
Hi, yes, I got your message
from Demany about the gem.
We're at the bank right now.
Oh. Did, uh... So does he want it?
Yes. Kevin's still interested.
We could actually be there--
It's like we discussed, right?
It's still, uh... It's still 175, right?
-Yes.
-In cash.
Yes, in cash. Like I said,
we're at the bank now.
-[KG] Did you tell him we're at the bank?
-[Liz] Kevin, yes. I told you.
-Howard, I gotta go.
-Okay.
I'll see you soon. Goodbye.
[Julia] You see? I told you.
[Howard] Arno? Hey, listen, no bullshit,
Kevin Garnett is coming to my office
right now with $175,000 cash. All right?
You said I got till Monday.
Today is still Monday
so I don't know if you're hearing this,
but Arno, this is real.
Kevin's really on the way.
He was just at the bank.
Come get your money, buddy.
I need the Celtic ring back.
-What happened to Friday?
-I know.
-It's Monday, Howie.
-I know what we said.
-What did we say?
-It was a short week. Pesach.
What happened to your face?
Car accident. Okay?
-So let's--
-What do you need?
[Howard] I need the Celtic ring,
and I'm gonna give you
the Knicks ring. All right?
You know what that means.
Swap them out, please.
You've had this Knicks ring forever.
I just need the Celtic ring back.
All right?
-[Steve] No, no. No.
-What do you wanna do?
-I own that ring right now.
-I know, I know you do. And I'm--
So, I'll swap you the two rings
but I'm gonna put a 15% vig on this one.
And if you're not here by Friday,
it's gonna be the same thing.
Not gonna have a third ring.
Not gonna have to worry about that.
Make it a 16%,
I'm sorry I fucked you, all right?
Bubby, what's going on? You okay?
I'm very good. Everything's going good.
-Yeah.
-I promise you. I promise you.
Hey. There he is.
KG! Don't you got a game tonight? [laughs]
I got your chip right here, all right?
Game night.
[Liz] We've really gotta go.
Can we make this quick?
[Howard] You must be Liz?
We're gonna make it quick, absolutely.
-[buzzer sounds]
-Julia,
let's get these guys some Powerades.
-Powerades?
-By the way...
Water? Anything else?
[KG] That's fine, I'm okay. I'm good.
-They're cold, you know that.
-Howard, let me get a second.
-[Howard] Sure, sure. All right.
-[Liz] Need to be in Boston in 45 minutes.
-[KG] I got it. Two seconds.
-[Liz] We need to be in Boston...
-[Howard] That's my office.
-Let me holla at you, man.
-Fuck's going on, man?
-[door closes]
Ever since I met you, you've been giving
me the run around with everything.
What do you mean?
Feel like you're fucking with my emotions.
You're just playing with me at some point.
This hasn't been straight
since I came here.
-You understand?
-Why are you saying that?
I borrowed the opal is one thing,
I come back over here, I brought it back.
I brought it back. I didn't have
to bring it back, you understand?
I show up at the auction,
you have somebody bid against me,
all these fucking games?
What the fuck are you doing?
You don't think I notice?
You don't think I know none of this?
-It's complicated, KG.
-[sighs]
You see this face, do you see it?
Man, here's 165,000 right here. Cash.
I'm showing you
because it wasn't easy, man.
Six percent goes to Demany,
I've already taken that out, all right?
All right, I guess that's fair.
Let me get the fucking opal, man.
Let me get the fuck up out of here.
This opal's very valuable for you.
-[KG] Absolutely.
-I did that.
Get the fuck out...
[Howard] I respect you,
I respect your passion.
-[KG] Man.
-[Howard] Okay, I always have.
-Thought you was a fan too, man.
-I'm a fucking huge fan.
What'd you pay for this? Real shit.
What'd you pay for this right here?
That's not a fair question,
Kevin, all right?
We're talking months and months
of fucking my time.
I'm not gonna take the money back.
I mean, I did the deal now.
I'm just saying. Straight up, me and you,
-mano a mano.
-[doorbell chimes]
How much you pay for this?
Fuckin'... What'd I pay?
I paid a... This is...
-[buzzer sounds]
-I'm telling you, that's...
If I answer that question,
it's very misleading.
Why?
-I paid 100 grand, okay?
-So you doubled your money?
[Howard] I'm the joke here,
all right? I got fucked.
A million dollars is what
I was supposed to get.
I get a fucking what? Made 65 Gs?
You gave some niggas from Ethiopia
100 grand for something
you thought was worth a million dollars.
You don't see nothing wrong with that?
Ethiopian miners,
you know what these fucking guys make?
100 grand's 50 lifetimes
for these fucking guys.
A million dollars is more,
that's my point. Understand?
Well, you wanna win by one point
or fucking 30 points, KG, right?
I see you out there with the fucking
stadiums all booing you.
You're 30 up,
you're still going full tilt.
Let's see what Vegas...
What does Vegas got you guys at tonight?
Take a look. Let's see.
Hold on, are you serious?
You're gonna pull this up right here?
Look at this shit. The Sixers are supposed
to win the game tonight, they think.
I don't keep track of none of that shit.
They think on game seven,
you're not gonna get fucking 18 points.
They don't think
you're gonna get eight rebounds?
These guys don't know shit about ball.
What the fuck do they do?
Doesn't that make you want
to fucking kill them?
Doesn't that make you wanna say,
"Fuck you for doubting me"?
Doesn't that make you wanna step on
fucking Elton Brand's fucking neck?
Come on, KG, this is no different
than that. This is me.
All right? I'm not a fucking athlete,
this is my fucking way, this is how I win.
All right?
All the fucking hard work I do,
all the fucking ass kicking,
and the dues I pay.
You're not gonna score
on the big one, on game seven?
Fuck these people, right?
That's how you feel, I know you do.
So, look...
Let's fucking bet on this.
Let's bet on this shit.
I'm fucking gonna bet
all this money on you tonight, KG.
You're here to win, KG.
These fuckers don't know.
Them out fucking west,
do you think they fucking know you?
They don't know you. They don't know us.
It's about fucking winning.
It's about you.
And I saw your fucking conviction,
your fucking honesty.
And your fucking magic.
[KG] Howard, you're fucking crazy, man.
KG, do you even understand
how fucking great of a game
you're gonna have tonight? I know it.
-Listen...
-We're a team tonight, KG.
This is a fucking lock-in.
It's a fucking feeling.
We both have it. They don't know.
You and I know, all right?
-[cell phone chimes]
-[man] Nice fucking trim.
-Nice fuckin' watch, too.
-[Julia sighs]
What the fuck are...
Hey, do you mind watching the space
while I run to the bathroom?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
I can leave you guys alone in here?
Go handle your business, sweetheart.
Do you want company?
I don't think so, but next time maybe.
[buzzer sounds]
Hey, hey, hey. I'm looking for Howard.
-I'm sorry, we're closed.
-He gave me a fucking fake Rolex.
I'm sorry, I don't know anything
about that, sir.
Please calm down.
I don't know anything about that.
Let me talk to you about this.
You gotta help me.
I'm sorry, I'm busy.
This is gonna be one of the best nights
of our fucking life.
Howard. Howard.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on.
Where are you? Hey.
Howard, what the fuck
is going on?
-Take this.
-What is this?
I need you to listen to me carefully.
I booked you on a blade, okay? You're
gonna land on top of the Mohegan Sun.
Okay.
There's a bet in that bag.
I want you to take all of it,
all of it inside the bag
and place it on that bet.
-How much is in the bag?
-There's a lot.
I don't want you to think about that.
All right?
I don't even look at it
until you get there, and you take it out,
and give it to the teller.
-Understand?
-I got it.
I'm gonna fuck the living shit
out of you tonight.
-You know that?
-I wish I could kiss you.
-You gotta go.
-[Julia] Okay.
-Get going. Get going.
-All right, love you. Bye.
[Julia] Thank you, guys. Thank you.
See you, guys.
[buzzer sounds]
Let's get this over with.
Arno. You're never
gonna believe this shit.
Believe what?
We're about to hit so goddamn big.
KG was just here. You saw him, right?
I gave him the gem. He's gonna fuck up
the money line so bad tonight.
Howard, where's the money right now?
It's on the way right now.
It's on the way to the casino.
-[Arno] What are you talking about?
-Buddy!
[Buddy] What the fuck
is going on in there?
-Girl that went to the bathroom?
-I ain't seen her.
-She didn't get back here?
-No.
-[Howard] What are you not getting?
-No, it's in this room right now.
Go get her now. Bring her back.
-Hey. Hit the buzzer.
-Open the fucking door!
For what? What am I opening the door for?
-Come and buzz me out.
-[Nico] I got it.
-What are they doing?
-[Buddy] Let's go.
-[Phil] No. Listen.
-[Arno] You're saying what?
Get your hands off me.
What the fuck are we doing?
It's gonna make sense to you in about
two fucking minutes. Listen to what--
-I'm listening.
-You're gonna do what I tell you.
Listen, you fucking goon,
I'm telling you something good--
-Listen.
-[Phil] Come here.
-[Howard] Arno?
-[indistinct shouting]
-[Howard] Arno, Arno.
[Phil] Get the fucking machine now!
[Howard] I wanna give you your money.
[Phil] Shut the fuck up!
I'll show you how.
Hey, come on, come on.
[Howard] No, no, no!
-[screaming]
-Got your attention now?
I'll drop you on your fucking head!
You hear me?
Gimme the word. I let him go.
-I got kids, help me up.
-You gonna call him?
-I'll call! Please.
-Get that bitch down here now!
-All right, take me up.
-[Phil] Get him up.
-Get him up.
-[groaning]
There you go.
Listen to me.
Get yourself together. All right?
Yeah, I want you to make that call.
You hear me?
Give me a fucking second, please.
You have plenty of time.
After you make the call.
My heart.
[Phil] Call this girl up,
I want her back here now.
[cell phone chimes]
She's in Mohegan Sun.
[Nico] Yeah, come on. Let's go.
-Put it on speaker.
-[dial tone sounds]
-[dialing]
-There we go.
This motherfucker...
Come on, come on.
[breathing heavily]
-[Howard] I can't, I'm sorry.
-[Phil] This fucking guy. Unbelievable.
I'm sorry. I really am. I am sorry.
I mean, fuck this!
You're a moron.
-[Phil] I'll do it. Are you kidding me?
-[Nico] Fuck him.
[Phil] He's not worth it.
Put that shit away.
-What are you doing?
-[Arno] Buzz us out.
What are you doing? Why am I
buzzing? Why are you going?
Just buzz me the fuck out.
-Watch the fucking game.
-Buzz me the fuck out.
-You'll be happy with the results.
-Buzz me out.
I'm telling you now, before I put
your head through the fucking glass.
All right, I'll buzz you out.
I'll buzz you out. All right?
-[buzzer sounds]
-Fuck it.
Now close that door. Close it.
Come on, buzz me out.
What are you doing?
-[door rattling]
-Open the fucking door.
-Come on.
-[banging on door]
-This cocksucker.
-[Arno] Howard, open the door.
[doorbell chimes]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm not buzzing you out.
Arno, Arno.
-The Sixers shouldn't even be there.
-[knocking on door]
You understand?
[Arno] No, no,
she's at the Mohegan Sun sportsbook.
[Phil] Mohegan Sun sportsbook.
Get over... Get over there now.
You know what she looks like, find her.
They're gonna get
to the guard and fold...
Howard. Open the door!
-I know you're upset, Arno.
-Of course I am.
I'm trying to fucking
make this all work for you.
-[Arno] Open the fucking door!
-NBA doesn't want the Sixers to win,
they got fucking--
There's no money in that, you understand?
The refs know that. They want stars.
-Buzz us the fuck out, Howard.
-Stars get 'em fucking ratings.
-Right now.
-[Phil] Open the door.
-Hey, this is fucking bulletproof.
-Open it now!
[Howard] You're gonna hurt yourself.
That doesn't work.
-Phil. Phil.
-I'm telling you to open it.
Arno, I'd duck,
you're gonna get killed.
-[Phil] That motherfucker.
-[Howard] Listen to me.
Thank you.
I'm talking to Arno. Enough of you.
-You better open this fucking door.
-[Howard] Listen to me.
I got something for you.
You realize all he's gotta do
is get the opening tip,
-he's got to get the...
-[Arno] Buzz that fucking thing open.
[Howard] You know how many rebounds
this guy's gonna get, Arno?
You know? Who is that?
Who are you talking to?
Who did you call?
[Nico] Open the fucking door, dick!
[Howard] Okay.
[phone dialing]
[indistinct conversation]
[banging on door]
-[Dinah on phone] Yeah?
-[Howard] Dinah, it's me.
Make it quick...
ConEd called the office.
There is a fucking leak.
There's a gas leak on Pinoak.
For crying out loud, Howard.
So they're evacuating
the whole block.
Just slow down? You're not making sense.
[Howard] Get the kids outta there.
You and the kids go to Amy's.
-Why'd they call the office...
-Stay at Amy's.
I don't know why they called me.
-It's not making any sense.
-I'm not here to argue with you.
-I'm looking out the window right now.
-Dinah, get the kids outta the house.
I'm frightened, okay?
-You're freaking me out.
-[Howard] Get out, go to Amy's
-and do not leave there till I get home.
-Oh, my God.
You promise me?
Stay in the house. Okay?
-Okay. You'll meet us there?
-Yes.
-[Phil] Let me tell you something, prick.
-Thank you.
Open the fucking door!
[man] Last year, I made $125 million.
I don't even know what to do
with my money anymore.
I have nobody to spend it with,
nobody to enjoy my life with anymore.
It's horrible.
Today is a big day for me.
I met you, you're hot.
You wanna have a drink
when we get there?
[TV announcer speaking indistinctly]
-Hey.
Okay, so I'm betting on the Celtics,
parlay three way, money, I don't know,
plus tip. Here, you just have to...
So, you wanna parlay three ways.
Make sure when you put it in,
it's exactly that.
I will. How much you want on it?
-I'm not sure. You're gonna have to...
-Oh, okay.
-Chad?
-[Chad] Yeah.
Give me a minute?
I just have to have
my supervisor count this, okay?
[Julia] Okay.
-We're almost there.
-One second.
[machine beeping]
-[yelling]
-[crowd cheering]
Come on. Let's go.
I'm feeling this. Feeling this.
Beautiful.
[indistinct commentary on TV]
[Howard] This is it, boys. This is it.
-Go ahead. Tell me.
-[Julia on phone] Hey...
[Julia speaking indistinctly]
[stammers] Okay, listen. Listen, say it.
Say the whole ticket out loud.
I want you to say it really loud.
Give me a second.
I want some people to hear it.
Hang on.
Hang on. Say the whole ticket.
Go ahead.
-[Julia] I put 155 on the three-way bet.
-[Howard] Yeah.
Garnett's points plus his rebounds
with the Celtics money line
with the Celtics to win the opening tip.
[Howard] Right. Read the whole ticket.
Read the whole ticket.
-Okay. So, it says here to win...
-You having a good time?
-Yes.
-...$1,229,000.
Did you fucking hear that number?
That's enough.
You don't have to say any more.
The bet's in. The bet's in, okay?
[Nico] Fuck you.
I'm taking you to the fucking...
The Ritz Carlton,
the Grand Cayman, all right?
-With a fucking jacuzzi.
-Okay, sure.
-All right, rub that tattoo for me.
-Okay, okay, I love you.
Okay, here we go.
We grab this tip
and we're in business, boys, all right?
Pound that chest, baby.
This is it. We gotta get this.
This is right out the gate.
Right out the gate.
-Come on, man.
-[announcer] Headline in today's
-Boston Globe, "One or done."
-[Howard] Come on.
Get that tip.
Let's go get that fucking tip.
[announcer] ...not only for the season,
but maybe for this big-3 hour
of Garnett, Pierce and Allen.
And that's a long way off...
-Get that! Yes! Yes!
-[Howard clapping]
Fuck, we would have been fucked
if we didn't get that.
That was the fucking biggest part
of the whole goddamn parlay right there.
That was huge. I knew he was gonna
win that. I knew he was gonna win that.
All right. Get set...
It's been a defensive battle
almost every game. Blocked by Pierce.
One! One rebound! Boom!
That's one. That's fucking one.
Look at that. Look at that.
Right out the fucking gate.
The man... The man's feeling the gem!
Go, get it, get it.
-Garnett down low against...
-Go, go finish, finish it.
Hey. Yes! All right, that's fucking it.
That's the first shot of the game,
he fucking hit it. That's three now.
Two plus that fucking rebound.
That's three out of the 26.
Okay, I bet on, um, the Celtics.
Specifically Kevin Garnett.
Okay. Two good bets.
Celtics are winning and
Garnett's got nine and seven,
so that's 16 right now
on your way to 26, you said, right?
[man 1] Oh, my God.
The gorgeous one is here.
-[man 2] Not even halftime yet.
-Hey, twice in one day. I can't believe it.
How are you
from the helicopter to here?
How you doing, baby?
I can't get you out of my mind.
[both chuckling]
-You're funny.
-Oh, you're hot, baby.
-You're definitely hot.
-Yeah.
[man 1] Is your money on Celtics?
Let me see, baby.
-[Julia] Is he gonna shoot?
-Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
[man 2] Come on, Garnett,
that one's gonna help.
-Fuck!
-[man 2] Come on.
-He should have gotten that one.
-He missed a shot, who cares?
-I have a great idea for halftime, okay?
-What's that?
[man 1] I'd like you
to come up to my room.
I hired a chef, I'm in penthouse A,
and I got you, it's gorgeous.
Best views. Who could ask
for more than that?
Thank you.
-I love you.
-[Julia] All right.
-I'll see you there.
-[Julia] Okay. I will...
Penthouse A, penny room. Okay, baby?
-[Julia] Yes, got it.
-[man 1] Nice. Can't wait to see you.
-[Julia] Okay, bye.
-Kevin Garnett...
-[man 2] Wow.
-The fucking worst.
-[man 2] He's like a cartoon.
Are you okay?
-Oh...
-What happened?
[announcer] ...in the second half,
which is coming up next.
-I gotta go.
-[man 2] You need help?
[Julia] Thank you so much
for your help.
This is the beauty of betting.
This is the beauty of betting, you know?
I'm fucking pulling for the Celtics,
a Knicks fan...
If the fucking
12-year-old version of me
saw me right now,
he'd be like, "What the fuck?"
[man] Everybody's talking
about this fucking big bet.
Tell them to come over here.
[man] So it's gotta be her.
He's with me.
We're gonna fucking snatch her
and bring her back.
Boss, boss. Absolutely.
[Doc Rivers] I need everyone in here
to lock in.
KG. Look at KG.
Remember this.
If you wanna go quickly, do it alone.
But if you wanna go far,
you do it together.
We're like roaches.
And you can't kill us.
Quit fucking passing. Get it to him.
And another and another.
And shoot. Shoot! Shoot!
Fuck, that shit, fucking Doc.
Fucking threw his rhythm off.
He took him out of the game.
Fuck, man. That's your fault.
You see that other guy though, Phil?
One of your boys from Boston.
You got some boys in Boston?
You'll see who I'm talking-- Hang on.
This fucker,
is that one of your boys, that fat fuck?
Looks like you.
Looks like one of your boys.
That's a fucking rebound. That's it.
Three more, three more. Way to go.
What does that say up there?
What is the score? Are they winning?
-They're winning. Winning by three points.
-[Howard] Another rebound!
Fuck that shit. He fucking fouled him.
Doesn't matter, he grabbed it, he had it.
That counts as one.
Now what are we at? 23?
All right, last possession.
Let's go. Get it.
Pick it up.
All right, that's it. That's it!
Shoot that shit. Come on, K.
Shoot it. Shoot it.
[yelling happily]
Oh!
Holy, fuck, yeah! They fuckin' got it.
Just, fucking, that's all the gem.
It's all the gem.
We're at 25 now! One more.
One more fucking point.
Either a rebound or a fucking basket.
Anything. Either one, we fucking got this.
All right, one more. Just need one more.
-Oh, my God.
-[Julia] Hi.
Come on in. Three times in one day.
-I know, I know.
-Unbelievable.
I believe it's you.
Where's your boyfriend?
-Why don't we watch the game?
-Without a doubt.
Go ahead, honey. Sit down,
make yourself comfortable.
[Julia] How do I--
Where's the remote? What do I do?
The iPad's over there,
do what you gotta do with the iPad.
Look, I gotta take a shower, okay?
I really gotta take a shower.
I gotta clean up. Gotta get myself washed.
That plane ride, got me all messed up
and everything else.
So what I want you to do.
If that doorbell rings, okay?
I got my friends, okay, coming in,
or I got the food coming, okay?
You just answer it
and let 'em in, okay, baby?
-Okay. All right.
-[man] Please.
[announcer] Garnett.
[Howard shouts] That's it. That's it.
Thank you. [kisses]
That's it. Okay, that's two that's done.
We got that. Two.
Just gotta win now.
Celt's gotta win and we're fucking done.
We're done, Arno.
[man] What do you got?
What's the score, baby?
68-73 Boston.
[man] 68? What? In the fourth?
You wanna call down,
just cancel the fucking food?
I wanna go out. Baby, I love
that you're into this game.
[crowd on TV chanting] Defense. Defense.
[announcer] Holiday...
trying to get rid of Brandon Bass,
tries it again.
Up and under, shot misses.
Allen on the rebound.
Push it. Push... Push it.
Push it, go, to the fucking hole.
Get it, KG, get it!
Ah, don't fucking miss that.
Don't miss that. It's all right.
-...with 57 seconds remaining...
-It's all right.
KG's gonna hit this fucking shot.
Let's ice this shit.
Sink this shot. Sink it, sink it. Come on.
Feel it. Feel it...
Feel it, come on.
He's got the gem. He's got the gem,
feel that fucking gem.
With 15 of 16 from the line, again,
only taken four here in the second half.
Oh, fucking cock.
It's all right, it's all right.
All right, we're up and up. We're up
and up. This is not that big of a deal.
This'll just fucking help seal it.
But we're good.
No talk.
Just fucking do your shit, man.
Do your shit. Do your shit.
When Pierce fouled out,
there was a little over
-four minutes remaining.
-You got this shit.
Celtics led by three.
[yells]
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. All right,
the truth fucking feels it.
I feel it. I'm confident now.
I'm confident.
Don't let 'em shoot that,
don't let 'em shoot that.
Get that, grab that shit. Yes!
Oh! Oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah! [laughs] Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Holy fucking shit. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Howard? Did we just win?
Oh, my fucking God!
Are you kidding me?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, shit. Oh, my God, baby. I love you.
I love you. I love you....
[chuckling] I love you, I love you...
[repeating] I love you, I love you...
I.. [sighs] Arno!
-[Howard bangs on glass]
-I did it!
-[Arno] He fucking did it.
-All right.
-You always believed, Arno.
-[Arno] He fucking did it.
I know, I know, thank you.
[repeating] Thank you...
No, you, you. I love you.
I'm so happy, I fucking...
It's going down. It's going down.
[Phil] Get off the phone, man, you won.
You made your point. Let's go.
You've made your mark.
[Howard] Are you listening? Hi.
Yes, just cash it in, okay?
And make sure they fucking
walk you to the car.
All right? I'm gonna book you a plane.
-[Arno] Howard.
-[door buzzes]
-All right, I'll call you back.
-[Arno] Son of a bitch.
-I can't fucking believe it.
-[Howard] I knew it, Arno.
[gun fires]
[Arno] What? What the fuck
did you just do? What the fuck?
-Shut up. Get me bags now.
-[Arno] What did you just do? You...
Hey, get off me. Shut the fuck up.
Or you'll wind up next to him,
you hear me? Don't fucking confuse me.
-Get off me.
-[Phil] Fuck.
[Arno] Take your hands
off of me right now.
[Phil] Go ahead.
Right now, go ahead. Do it.
What do you wanna say? Do it. Do it!
I want outta here.
Let me outta here. Let me out!
[Phil] Go get the bags now.
I'll fix this.
Get over here. Stay right there.
Stay right fucking there.
Come on, let's go.
[indistinct shouting]
-[door rattling]
-Where you going now, motherfucker?
Get over here.
[gun fires]
[interviewer] You're headed back to the
Conference Finals, how are you feeling?
When you win, it's all that matters.
You know? The big be quiet,
the big shut up, you know?
Killin' doubters, killin' haters.
Bring it in, bring it in...
That's a lot of fucking money, right?
And a personal one to you, bruh.
[interviewer] ...celebrated your 36th
birthday. Everyone saying he's too old...
That's some strong shit.
Oh. That's my nigga right there, boy.
Look at that motherfucker, man.
I know that guy, I know that guy.
My dad sold a ring to him.
Eddie, I can't think.
Amy, he was naked in the trunk, okay?
I'm calling the police.
All the dues and everything
that I put into this,
you wouldn't think that
I would show up to game sevens?
Yeah, that's a joke.
[interviewer] Paul Pierce
bows out of this one.
He goes to the bench,
did you feel that you needed
to shoulder his load for...
Well done. Congratulations.
[interview continues indistinctly]
[KG] It's not down to one guy,
so I know we all share that responsibility
and we did a good job. You know?
In the end, I felt like it was just me
and the rock, um, nothing else.
[interview continues indistinctly]
Oh, my God, Wayne.
-Thank you so much.
-All right, baby.
My pleasure. A lot of money.
I want you to come to the Avalon,
have one drink.
No, I can't. I gotta go, bye, baby.
-No, I gotta go.
-Let's have one drink.
We can go now.
-[Phil] Nico, I got this.
-[KG speaking indistinctly on TV]
-Don't worry.
-[Phil] Okay, got it. Let's go, let's go.
Go, go! Find their fucking cameras?
All right, go, go, come on.
-[Nico] Okay, I got 'em, I got 'em.
-[glass breaking]
-[Phil] Nico?
-[Nico] I can't find the cameras.
[Phil] And make sure
you get all those electronics.
Get that video tape.
Put it in the fucking bag!
[ambient electronic music playing]
["L'amour toujours (Small Mix)"
by Gigi D'Agostino playing]
[woman singing]
I still believe in your eyes
I just don't care
What you've done in your life
Baby, I'll always be here
By your side
Don't leave me waiting
Too long
Please come by
I, I, I, I still believe
In your eyes
There is no choice
I belong to your life
Because I, I live
To love you someday
You'll be my baby
And we'll fly away
And I'll fly with you
I'll fly with you
[music continues]
[man singing]  I'll fly with you
I'll fly with
Every day and every night
I always dream that
You are by my side
Oh, baby, every day
And every night
Well, I said everything's
Gonna be all right
And I'll fly with you
I'll fly with you
[music continues]
[music fades out]